Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: everyone Why don't we just take a quick moment before we begin?
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Close our eyes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Take a deep breath.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Shit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: and Tick.
David S. Kong: Two more breaths at your own pace, and just release…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Whatever was going on in your day.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just release whatever…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Take one…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Go into some emptiness.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hopefully now, you're starting to be in an empty place.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Take one more breath.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just really feel… The emptiness of the space around me.
David S. Kong: And keep your eyes closed.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you As you start to… Enter your character.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Start to imagine yourself.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Inside your dragonet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Feel your wings.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Ill.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Your fingers and your claws.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And start to just feel the personality of your character.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And how he likes to feel.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It makes him… Smile and laugh and angry.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just kinda stretch your wings a little bit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And feel yourself in that character.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And how good it feels to have wings. And how good it feels to have… An awesome fucking life.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And cool new powers and abilities that you just discovered.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A few hours ago.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And also how fucking epic this day has been, or those past 24-36 hours has been.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as you now.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Feel embodied in your characters.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Feel free to open your eyes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And we begin… With a scene again.
David S. Kong: Outside of the storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: With these two humanoid figures staring, standing and staring at some kind of strange energy meter device.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And emotional at what they're seeing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And commenting.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That these signatures are impossible, how could this be here? But that it's unmistakable.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That indeed, on this strange island on the other side of the storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There are these four unmistakable signatures.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And the scene closes with them saying, They're our firstborn here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… As we exit this vessel and cross through the barriers of the storm, Back into the circular island.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We encounter… Honestly, a pretty different scene.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As we shift.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We encounter, inside of… the ship, or inside the statue of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This scene of… The four of you.
Eric Rosenbaum: can.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you sitting.
David S. Kong: Inside… A cockpit.
David S. Kong: Which… Again, as you kind of just step back for a second on how awesome this day has been.
David S. Kong: I think for all of you, probably the coolest day of your entire lives. Maybe, maybe not, we'll see, you can all reflect on that in a moment.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you but.
David S. Kong: Each of you, sitting… In a seat that, by the way, to re-emphasize.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: is.
David S. Kong: Custom made for dragonets like it's like perfectly your sized.
David S. Kong: And it was like that when you showed up. There's other kind of features in this hall and this other space that are not made for dragonets, but these are made for dragonets.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And these seats feel good again.
David S. Kong: Very, very much.
David S. Kong: The old chair, the old familiar chair that you've loved to sit in your whole lives.
David S. Kong: And as you sit in your seats.
David S. Kong: Reflecting on what has occurred over the past, you know, day or so. You're enjoying this amazing festival with your Dragonet community.
David S. Kong: Some kind of crazy egg appears that you go and hug, you have some insane vision of some terrible land with a burnt red sky, a dragonet dying, a divine light coming, and
David S. Kong: You somehow becoming that light, shooting across some time-space continuum thing, ending up in the palm of the Wanderer, waking up, having weird, strange abilities and sensations. There's food machines and other things interacting and waking up all over the island, and then you make your way to the Wanderer, somehow get inside, and are here.
David S. Kong: And we ended last session with each of you.
David S. Kong: Trying to make the wanderer do things collectively.
David S. Kong: And if you'll remember, you had tried to make the wanderer walk.
David S. Kong: And as you had started that process, energy started to surge throughout the space as you were all collectively imagining the Wanderer actually doing something.
David S. Kong: And as that energy surged throughout the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: We concluded.
David S. Kong: And we'll begin this session now, our final session.
David S. Kong: I'd love for each of you to describe
David S. Kong: How are you feeling right now?
David S. Kong: Sitting in these seats, inside the chest of the Wanderer, which all of you know, and have been around your entire lives, and, you know, Sculpit and.
David S. Kong: Tony, for both of you, you know, the Wanderer is a particularly special place.
David S. Kong: And y'all flew through the eyeball of the Wanderer, and ended up in this weird place, and, you know, there are these, like, statues with lasers inside. I mean, it's been a day.
David S. Kong: So, I'd love for each of you to begin by sharing about your character's state of mind, how you're feeling, and what it's like for you to be sitting in this pocket.
David S. Kong: you.
Mike Sackton: you.
Tim Sackton: So Heska.
Tim Sackton: As… A.
Tim Sackton: So as he sits in this, strange seat.
Tim Sackton: Connected… To this place that… Like.
Tim Sackton: You know, completely weird, unexpected turn of events.
Tim Sackton: of this day.
Tim Sackton: And this surge of power that's left him feeling,
Tim Sackton: very…
Tim Sackton: I think he's not quite sure what to feel about this. Like, on the one hand, he wants to go explore, and the other hand, he's like, what's going on? But at the moment, the let's go explore motivation is winning out, and he is turning and looking at everybody.
Tim Sackton: has…
Tim Sackton: Just moments ago, at least several of us had been like, let's make the statue walk. And he's looking around like, let's get going, team. Let's trot into the ocean. I've always wanted to see how far we can go.
Tim Sackton: And so there is this…
Tim Sackton: balance between buzzing excitement and abject terror, but at the moment, the buzzing excitement is winning.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nino's always been like, yo, think bigger, man. Think bigger. Trying to give himself the little pep talk.
Eric Rosenbaum: And never quite, you know, made it happen.
Eric Rosenbaum: With folks around him to, like, get something started. And so today, sitting in this cockpit, he's like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe… maybe I gotta think even bigger than… a restaurant concept, although admittedly, it was a very cool concept.
Eric Rosenbaum: Actually, maybe this statue thing, maybe the Wanderer could be part of the rest, maybe the Wanderer, like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Serves you your, or maybe, oh, it could date, oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: Dancing statue, come to the restaurant for the
Eric Rosenbaum: We Sticks and Swings is a good concept. Maybe that'll be the one we retire to.
Eric Rosenbaum: We gotta go big, you know?
Eric Rosenbaum: And go far.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe we could get out of here.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe we could explore with this thing.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wonder where we could take it to?
David S. Kong: Like, outside the island you mean, explore?
Eric Rosenbaum: Into the Beyond.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oop.
Eric Rosenbaum: Always wondered what's out there.
Eric Rosenbaum: Never had a giant statue to play with.
Mike Sackton: culprits Some.
Mike Sackton: Kind of torn, he's kind of looking around and, like, poking at everything, like… This is so…
Mike Sackton: Weird and different than, like… How does it work?
Mike Sackton: Like, he's always collected kind of odd tales and odd bits of lore as kind of a side project.
Mike Sackton: And that side of him that's sort of, like, fascinated in the unusual is, like.
Mike Sackton: totally entranced by this, and kind of wants to, like, experiment and see how it all works. On the other hand, he's a little bit like…
Mike Sackton: Isn't this kind of, like…
Mike Sackton: big for us? Like… Like, I don't want to be in the center stage of world events. Like, do we… do we have to be in the center stage of world events? Like, like, why is this statue so big? And, like, so… so doing what we said, like, is that…
Mike Sackton: Are we sure that we're, like, the right people for this?
Mike Sackton: Maybe we are! Like, like, let's be great, but like… are we sure?
Mike Sackton: Like, maybe we figure out how it works before we, like, charge into the great beyond.
Mike Sackton: Just a thought, like, for your consideration.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): For little Tony, this is like,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is like going on on a cruise ship vacation for the first time ever. It's like this, just this whole new experience, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): he's not excited exactly, like, to get away and explore, and he's not really captivated by how does this all work, and what will happen. It's more like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, what a wonderful vacation, like, for… for 3 or 4 days, we're gonna get around and out there and see what's going on. He's built this all in his mind, he's disappointed he hasn't brought a swimsuit.
Eric Rosenbaum: But he's.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He's also like, he has heard because he is a much more of a littoral creature rather than a sea creature. He's only heard like the stories of the stories of like big whales and like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): giant sharks and things like that, so he's a little curious to get out to the deep water to see if there are, like, new people to talk to. Like, what kind of stories do big whales have?
David S. Kong: Mmm.
Eric Rosenbaum: And sing some tunes to them.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah. He also thinks like, if he can get rocks from the bottom of the ocean, like way out there, like the value, it's going to blow the whole market out of the water. But he's, he sees the business opportunity.
Tim Sackton: You're in two.
Eric Rosenbaum: Could be.
Tim Sackton: It's a big statue.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): In the smooth pebble market, yeah.
Tim Sackton: It can reach down pretty far. That's good thinking, little Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): thank you, yeah.
David S. Kong: And as a reminder to all of you, I know this is all a lot, a lot, a lot in a very short period of time, but remember that when you flew through the Wanderer's eye, and as you were traversing down the mechanical shaft of its throat into the heart?
David S. Kong: You suddenly became way more powerful. So just, you know, remember that. Like, and I know you're settling now into these chairs, but you do, like, sense in your systems that something has changed.
David S. Kong: That you could try to, you know, play around with a little bit. Now… I mean, there's a lot to play with. There's both your.
Eric Rosenbaum: internal.
David S. Kong: ourselves as having expanded somehow.
David S. Kong: And this idea of, like, control and precision and power is, like, really coursing through you in a pretty awesome way.
David S. Kong: But then again, you're also sitting on cockpits in the heart of the Wanderer right now, and you kinda got it to, like, sorta move a little bit by just thinking about it together? So maybe that's also pretty cool. There's kind of a lot of things to consider right now, you wanna do.
David S. Kong: So, what do you want to do?
Tim Sackton: Let's go for a walk.
Tim Sackton: That's the size.
Eric Rosenbaum: Lift the right foot.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Which one?
Eric Rosenbaum: Where's the right?
Tim Sackton: Wait, who's right? Our right or the statue's right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, wait, wait, wait. Slow down. And, and Zeno like lifts his own right foot. It's like, okay, just watch me and do, and do what I do and we'll make this.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna think really hard about my right foot lifting up.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, with your eyes open so you can see my own, what I'm doing. Ready? Okay. One.
Tim Sackton: No, it hasn't.
Eric Rosenbaum: Stay tuned.
Tim Sackton: Get with those eyes closed.
Eric Rosenbaum: We'd have him to knock this thing over, you guys!
Mike Sackton: So.
Eric Rosenbaum: Pulls down, it might not be able to get up.
Mike Sackton: No. Let's do an maybe okay. So here's the thing about experiments. Right? You start with a little safe one.
Mike Sackton: Like, like a hand? Or a toe? Right foot, right foot. No, no, because then we'll fall, we'll fall.
Mike Sackton: Cool, takes a breath, okay.
Tim Sackton: Think really hard about lifting the right foot.
Mike Sackton: So everybody, here, let's just… Here's an idea.
Tim Sackton: Is anything happening?
Mike Sackton: Maybe we should consider it.
David S. Kong: Y'all gotta make a decision first on what's happening first.
Mike Sackton: Skaldin's not thinking about the right foot. We're just gonna fall over.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Let's try moving the arm first and figure out how it works.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): All right, I suggest that everyone types in chat, what we're thinking of moving, and then we all hit enter simultaneously.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay, that's great.
David S. Kong: Perfect.
Mike Sackton: So here's what I would say. If we move the… The right hand.
David S. Kong: No, no. Scalpa, stop talking. Scott says everybody.
Mike Sackton: Great head.
David S. Kong: Ted, put it into the chat, and then I'm gonna say 3, 2, 1, and then hit enter, and that's what each of you is thinking about moving right now. Are you ready? You have it in the chat, where you want to move? Yep. Okay. 3, 2, 1, enter.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh my God, okay, all right.
David S. Kong: Now, now what we're gonna do is, okay.
David S. Kong: Each of you rolls a d20. Okay.
David S. Kong: Tony?
David S. Kong: You are rolling an insight check. Heska is rolling an acrobatics check. Sculpet is rolling an arcana check. And Zeno is rolling a performance check.
Tim Sackton: 22.
Eric Rosenbaum: What'd you get? 12.
Eric Rosenbaum: I rolled a 12 with a natural 1.
Mike Sackton: 24.
David S. Kong: Who rolled the 24? Mike?
Mike Sackton: Gulp it, yeah.
David S. Kong: Golfo rolled a 24, and who else rolled above a 20?
Tim Sackton: Me.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Yeah, so basically… What ends up happening is, You get the sense.
David S. Kong: And part of what's interesting here is as you're sitting in these chairs, like
David S. Kong: And again, you haven't tried this anywhere else. You've only been trying this, obviously, sitting in the chairs.
David S. Kong: But you, you do just, you do get a little bit of a sensation, it's not as though, like
David S. Kong: Like, when you move your arm, you feel like the thing is moving, but it's more like…
David S. Kong: You feel a little bit of a sensation that the right foot, in this case, does just have the slightest little bit of… I mean, it's definitely not moving, but it feels like it's energized to move, sort of like there's an intention there, even though nothing is happening.
David S. Kong: And same thing with the right fingers closing on the hand. You get a sensation.
Eric Rosenbaum: that.
David S. Kong: It wants to close, but nothing is actually happening.
David S. Kong: And, and also by the way, just as a side note, you can't see shit. It's not like you're like, it's not like currently you can like see through the eyes of the wanderer out in the ocean. You're sitting in a cockpit right now, but there's no.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh…
David S. Kong: At least currently, you have not figured out any way to, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Under Muni.
Mike Sackton: So, I think we all…
David S. Kong: The only link that you have to the statue right now is this, like, you try to do something, you have a sensation in your own hand, and, you know, right, you know.
David S. Kong: You know, leg or whatever, but…
David S. Kong: It's one way, it's not like you moved and then Sancho moved right off.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay, guys, just wiggle all your toes, just wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. Just, like, we're gonna wiggle the toes.
Mike Sackton: But we got to do all the same thing at once. We got to focus and come together.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay, focus up, focus up.
Mike Sackton: Ready?
Mike Sackton: Right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no, what are we doing?
Mike Sackton: actually.
Eric Rosenbaum: us.
Mike Sackton: Wiggle the toes is great. We all know what toes are. They're like talons for those of you who don't know what toes are. Like wiggle, just wiggle the toes. Don't try to move. Just the wiggle, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, we still might fall over, but we'll learn something.
Mike Sackton: the wiggle.
Eric Rosenbaum: Before we die. Wiggle the toes.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Ready?
Tim Sackton: Let's do it. All right.
Mike Sackton: doesn't.
David S. Kong: Wait, wait. All four of you now actually like align together on wiggling your toes.
Mike Sackton: We're gonna wiggle the toe.
David S. Kong: All right. Just, you know, because you're fucking dragonettes on this shit, even though you're saying. We're going to do the exact same thing.
Eric Rosenbaum: I.
Mike Sackton: the.
David S. Kong: chat. You're saying this all out loud, but put into the chat.
Mike Sackton: should.
David S. Kong: on what you're actually thinking in your mind. Okay. All right. Here we go. Three, two, one, enter.
David S. Kong: Tony.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I want to wiggle my toes!
David S. Kong: Okay, each of you roll a d20 again. Again, according to the same things: Insight, Acrobatics, Arcana, and Performance.
Mike Sackton: I got a natural 20.
Tim Sackton: Four.
Eric Rosenbaum: 28.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Something in the teens.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay. This is a very strong success.
David S. Kong: You all feel, and this is fucking insane that this is actually happening, because you're like, and again, the Wanderer has not moved here. I'm going to change the POV for a second here.
David S. Kong: So, the Wanderer… it's a fucking statue, you know what I mean? That you are slowly starting to learn maybe is not just a statue and actually is designed for another purpose.
David S. Kong: But you actually feel the creaking of toes.
David S. Kong: Actually beginning to slightly creak and wiggle and what's crazy about the feeling in your talons.
David S. Kong: you have your own talons and the own feeling there, but something… it's like there's this other layer of awakening that is happening in your talons as you start to just kind of creak it a little bit. And it literally feels… it's that feeling of, like…
David S. Kong: after having slept for a super long time, and, like, you're coming back into your body, and it's sort of like, oh, you're stretching your arms for the first time, and what it feels like when you're waking up and that's happening, that's what this is like. It's like, these toes have not moved in fucking forever, but now it's like…
David S. Kong: Oh, shit. Toes. Sick.
David S. Kong: What do you do next?
Tim Sackton: Walk.
Tim Sackton: Come on, we can do it!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Don't I I feel it for for myself and maybe different for Stasha, but for me.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I like seeing where I'm going. Like, how do we even know where we're going right now?
Mike Sackton: Let's try and see.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Mike Sackton: Right.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Like, we gotta find them.
Mike Sackton: The eyes, right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: flew through them.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, they're up there somewhere.
David S. Kong: They're up there, they're somewhere, yeah.
Mike Sackton: But, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We gotta…
Mike Sackton: like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): open.
Mike Sackton: Find them? From here?
Mike Sackton: Like I felt like I had a foot.
Mike Sackton: That was weird, by the way.
Mike Sackton: Right? Like, we felt like toes, kind of in our toes, right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, but I usually feel toes in my toes, you know?
Mike Sackton: Yeah, but it was like… It was like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Someone else's. Yeah, that's true.
Mike Sackton: RTS.
Tim Sackton: Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. House guy has an idea.
Tim Sackton: Can we… Do we have to be sitting in these chairs to move the statue?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, good question.
Tim Sackton: Because if not.
Tim Sackton: One of us can fly outside.
Tim Sackton: And we can all just think the same thing.
Tim Sackton: That'll work, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: And, like, sit on top of the head.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: But how are we going to know what to think if that's the.
Tim Sackton: Tony can. Tony can telepathically communicate with all of us.
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's try it.
Mike Sackton: Everybody up out of your chairs.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): the.
Mike Sackton: Right?
Mike Sackton: Let's all. Let's all like stand. Let's fly up in the air. Right, right.
Tim Sackton: How about we wave?
Mike Sackton: To each other?
Tim Sackton: No, no, no, the statue.
David S. Kong: That makes more sense.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, okay, yes,
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's, let's, let's.
Mike Sackton: Let's raise our right hand and wave.
David S. Kong: No, that's it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's just wave both hands.
Tim Sackton: No, no, no.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes, yes, yes.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: We ain't bothered.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes. Yep. Both hands.
Tim Sackton: But think it, don't do it, just think it.
Mike Sackton: Okay, ready?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We do both.
Tim Sackton: Yes, you're allowed to do both.
Mike Sackton: What?
David S. Kong: you.
Mike Sackton: On the count of three, everybody think really hard.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I need a count of three. I'm already there.
Eric Rosenbaum: Just doing it.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
David S. Kong: Okay, so everybody's now actually waving their hands.
Tim Sackton: Waving our hands.
Mike Sackton: Not waving his hand. Sculptor is just thinking.
David S. Kong: Just stop thinking about waving his hand.
Mike Sackton: Maybe the Wanderer's hands.
David S. Kong: Yeah. Is anybody else thinking about waving hands?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: Of course.
Tim Sackton: But none of us are sitting in the chair in the chair and.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay.
Mike Sackton: Flying in the middle of the, like, off of the…
David S. Kong: Actually, yeah, roll, everybody roll 20, D20 again, according to the same checks.
Mike Sackton: 23.
Tim Sackton: 23.
David S. Kong: Sorry, 2323.
Tim Sackton: My… I'm a rogue, so the lowest I can roll is a 23.
David S. Kong: Are you serious?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): certain.
David S. Kong: Oh, I need to make this higher. There needs to be some drama here. Wait, wait, hold on.
David S. Kong: Wait, what's the lowest everybody can roll? Actually, this is good for me.
Tim Sackton: I'm the only one who can't roll high. Who can't roll high?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's that we have no idea what we're doing.
David S. Kong: Well, no, wait, wait, but seriously, I'm just curious. What is everybody's lowest roll?
Mike Sackton: 11.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): the 8.
David S. Kong: That's the lowest possible roll.
Mike Sackton: Tim's the only one with a… who's a.
Tim Sackton: I'm the only one who can only roll high, because I have the rogues have one of their main abilities is…
David S. Kong: And yours is 23, Tim?
Tim Sackton: My lowest is 23. Don't you remember Welby? Like.
David S. Kong: I know, I know, but Eric, what's your lowest roll?
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, I have a plus 11, so I can roll a 12 or higher, basically.
David S. Kong: Okay, great. Okay, alright, that's fine, that's fine. Alright, I'm making this more difficult so that there's at least a chance that
David S. Kong: all four of you can fail, because right now, that this is how I set it up, it's impossible for Tim to fail this without rolling a 1. Okay.
David S. Kong: And what were your roles one more time?
Tim Sackton: 23.
Mike Sackton: 23.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 20.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think it was 22.
Eric Rosenbaum: They aren't showing up in the thing, but…
David S. Kong: This is what happens, this is what happens.
David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer's arms do not wave. They do not.
David S. Kong: But… You all get the sense that
David S. Kong: If you were just… I don't know what it is, it's just, like, you feel, like, again, really strong, really powerful now, but you get the sense that it… you were just more something.
David S. Kong: Like more stronger, more tuned in, whatever you feel like it could be possible to move it.
David S. Kong: Without being in the seats, but right now you can't.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
David S. Kong: But it feels like… it feels like it's possible, which is, like, an interesting feeling.
Tim Sackton: Well…
Mike Sackton: 6…
Tim Sackton: I mean, does it really matter if we can see?
Eric Rosenbaum: No.
Mike Sackton: But yes, turns out vision's important.
Eric Rosenbaum: Are we standing on a cliff?
Eric Rosenbaum: Or no.
Tim Sackton: What if we just dive?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you know how shallow the water is right there compared to how big we are right now?
Mike Sackton: Like, and stone can break, you know that, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, we don't want to shatter this thing.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I've seen it happen.
Mike Sackton: When stone hits a certain angle, it cracks.
David S. Kong: Oh.
Mike Sackton: And there's pieces instead of a statue.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That is how you make little pebbles.
Mike Sackton: It is, but our goal here, Little Tony, is to find you the really cool pebbles, not make pedals out of.
Eric Rosenbaum: This statue?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's right. Stay big.
Mike Sackton: Hold on. Pebbles made of the statue would probably also be… But let's not go there.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There's no way to lose, is what I hear you say, though.
Mike Sackton: I'm glad you took such encouragement from my words, despite how they were meant.
David S. Kong: Alright, so what do you got, T.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, I don't know what I meant either.
David S. Kong: What are you doing? What are you guys doing?
Mike Sackton: Okay, are the seats… in the picture, the four seats we were sitting in were glowing and the other ones weren't?
Mike Sackton: that.
David S. Kong: Like, energized, yeah. Like, they were like…
Mike Sackton: stopped being energized when we flew out of them.
David S. Kong: They're still like shimmering, they're still like, you know, they're still a buzz.
Mike Sackton: Is there any, like, part of the, like.
Mike Sackton: Device that comes off without it feeling like it's breaking it.
Mike Sackton: Like, a cushion from a seat, or like, a piece of a…
David S. Kong: No, you can't take a piece of it. It's just, you can either sit in the little throne cockpit thing that's like sized perfectly for Dragonites or not.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Are there instructions?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, there's not, like, a manual next to the seat.
Tim Sackton: I'm just gonna think really hard about Emmanuel appearing in my hand, in the Wanderer's hand.
David S. Kong: Okay, cool. Anybody else doing that?
Mike Sackton: Well, are you saying that out loud or you just do it?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'm gonna say that out loud.
Mike Sackton: Oh, that's a good idea.
Eric Rosenbaum: dragon.
Mike Sackton: that.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're dragonets, can we even read?
David S. Kong: Okay, you're all thinking about…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's comic book form. Like we, it's all pictographic. Like it's not.
David S. Kong: Bam. Hit. Okay, everybody roll d20 towards your checks.
Tim Sackton: It's, 23 again.
Mike Sackton: 19.
Eric Rosenbaum: 15.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 22.
David S. Kong: Yeah, nothing happens.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice, nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: What is the…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What if… Let's see out of its eyes. I'm gonna close my eyes and look.
Eric Rosenbaum: Credit, credit.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Seeing out of the Wanderer's eyes while I'm in the chair.
Eric Rosenbaum: Are you going to suggest this to others or?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes, yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay. Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Well, I'll follow along.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm just like… Looking.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think this is gonna work better if we hum while we do it, so let's…
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Come while we concentrate, okay?
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm in the game, I'm in the game, the kingdom is…
Tim Sackton: Tesla cannot like match a tune to save his life, so everybody else.
Eric Rosenbaum: He's like, Can burn in the kitchen.
Tim Sackton: Is that working?
David S. Kong: Tell me, tell me your roles.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Guys hum louder.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Mike Sackton: 25?
Eric Rosenbaum: 25.
Tim Sackton: 25.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 19?
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: You feel, ok, ok, ok.
David S. Kong: There's a couple things that happen all at once.
David S. Kong: As all of you lock in and imagine yourselves opening the Wanderer's eyes.
David S. Kong: You feel two things, at least, that happen at once.
David S. Kong: First, because you're… wait, are your eyes closed right now, as you're imagining opening the Wanderer's eyes? Yeah. Everybody's eyes closed?
David S. Kong: Yep.
Mike Sackton: Gulp is just looking around.
David S. Kong: But you're thinking this.
Mike Sackton: Thinking, yeah. But he, like, is mostly looking at what other people are doing. But he's definitely thinking about seeing things.
David S. Kong: So this is for everybody that's on Sculpit right now.
David S. Kong: Each of you… Heskazino and Tony.
David S. Kong: When you open your eyes and imagine opening your eyes.
David S. Kong: You open your eyes.
David S. Kong: And what's crazy is your eyelids feel so heavy and crusty, again, sort of like you've been sleeping for fucking days, or maybe centuries.
David S. Kong: And there's this kind of creaking feeling of, like, the fucking gnarliest, like, eye boogers you can possibly imagine.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
David S. Kong: Thanks for opening.
David S. Kong: And what you see in front of you.
David S. Kong: Is a giant stone outstretched palm.
David S. Kong: and you see… In the distance… A storm.
David S. Kong: And amazing clouds, and… You're looking through the eyes of a wanderer.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And.
Eric Rosenbaum: day!
David S. Kong: Also, also, also, also… You feel almost like a voice in your head.
David S. Kong: If… it's more a sensation, but if the sensation had words, it would say something like, discovery unlocked.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it for you.
David S. Kong: Because you're, like, actually looking around?
David S. Kong: You have this weird fucking sensation because you can still see.
David S. Kong: Like, looking around the cockpit. But it's, like, overlaid over that is, like, another vision of what everybody else is seeing.
David S. Kong: And it's confusing. Like, it's like if you if you're you really you need to concentrate on which one you're seeing. You can't like, see them both at the same time.
Mike Sackton: When I see that, like, immediately, I'll close my eyes and try to pay attention to one, and then, like, open them and try to pay attention to another and see if.
David S. Kong: You can, with enough practice, you can kind of switch around, but you can definitely only do one or the other.
Mike Sackton: Right.
David S. Kong: with your consciousness.
Tim Sackton: Now we just have to figure out how to walk.
Mike Sackton: I'm going to start thinking about lifting his foot. I'm not going to say anything. Sculpt is just thinking, lift the right foot.
David S. Kong: Roll a d20.
David S. Kong: Oh, well, everybody else think about what you're doing. If you're is anybody else thinking about rolling foot?
Tim Sackton: No, I'm still just like.
Mike Sackton: I rolled a one.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
David S. Kong: Yeah, nothing happens.
Eric Rosenbaum: Statue begins tipping backwards slowly.
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's… guys, let's… let's look down at the feet, and then move one of the feet, just, like, shuffle forward a little bit, you know what I'm saying?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, let's do it.
David S. Kong: Okay, so are all of you, are all 4 of you doing this?
Tim Sackton: Yup.
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's go in.
Eric Rosenbaum: Move one foot.
David S. Kong: Sculpit, are you, are you part of this?
Mike Sackton: Yeah. I'll, like, when everybody's, like.
Mike Sackton: getting together, I'll be like, yeah, you're right, let's try this all together. I got enthusiastic.
David S. Kong: Okay, so now all of you are doing what? You're all looking down at the red foot and trying to move it?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Every roll d20? Just now, just, just, let's go fast. Just tell me, just tell me your rolls as quickly as you can. 32.
Eric Rosenbaum: 19.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 19.
David S. Kong: Stop it.
Mike Sackton: 50th.
David S. Kong: You feel, again, the creaking of your neck, and it is looking down at the right foot, and then you feel, like, the creaking of the foot, and it is moving.
Eric Rosenbaum: And.
Tim Sackton: going?
Eric Rosenbaum: Is the ground flat up ahead, or what?
David S. Kong: Yeah, I mean, ignore this a little bit. I mean, it is, like, a drop-off on the other side, but there's, like, flat area in front of you, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: And dish.
David S. Kong: I mean, relative to your size, which is, like, you know, hundreds of feet tall.
Mike Sackton: Are we like walking in one direction? What is our arc of vision?
David S. Kong: What does that mean?
Mike Sackton: Like, how much can we see? Are we, like, just seeing, like…
Mike Sackton: Like, look into one of his eyes.
David S. Kong: You have, like, you have, like, human perception.
Mike Sackton: that's.
David S. Kong: You're, you're, you're, you've got, like, whatever.
Mike Sackton: what.
David S. Kong: $160.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, but like we have to turn our head to look the direction.
David S. Kong: You have not… you just looked down. You just looked down and moved your phone.
Mike Sackton: Correct, yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: That's Ivy.
Mike Sackton: at…
Eric Rosenbaum: Is there anything we could stomp on?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Just to test the stopping.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, no, no, no. Or is there like a is there a nearby boulder that we could kick and see how far we can kick it?
Eric Rosenbaum: That's what I'm talking about, yes.
Mike Sackton: Maybe simple before, like… Can we, like… Yes!
Mike Sackton: Dap into the like Ocean, a bit, just, like, 1 inch.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, are we facing the water?
David S. Kong: No, you're facing inland. All the statues are facing inside.
Mike Sackton: Let's turn around and look. Let's just turn around. Very simple.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're definitely, we're going in the water.
Mike Sackton: Turn around.
Mike Sackton: the storm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Good, turn around, turn around.
David S. Kong: Okay, are you moving your feet to turn around?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: You're gonna, like, shuffle, shuffle turns?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Shuffle turn, shuffle turn.
David S. Kong: Okay, everybody roll d20. Are you all thinking the same thing?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Alright. What'd you got?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): one.
Eric Rosenbaum: 15.
Mike Sackton: 18.
David S. Kong: Eska?
Tim Sackton: 23.
David S. Kong: This is a partial success.
David S. Kong: You…
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
David S. Kong: Basically, like, kind of turn your hip.
David S. Kong: Creek, creek, creek, turn. And you kind of, like, take a little step up, and then a little step up. But you're definitely not very well balanced. You don't totally turn around. This is, like, kind of like a, you know, partial, partial success.
Tim Sackton: We can do it!
Tim Sackton: Just Practice takes perfect.
Tim Sackton: Doesn't somebody have, like, you know…
Tim Sackton: Can somebody hype us up here?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: I was just looking at my hype man skill. Yes, what.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: I don't think walking in a statue is something any of us have done before, so…
Eric Rosenbaum: Alright. You know what? Let's not try to just shuffle spin again. We are going to put all the weight on a ball of one foot, and then, like, spin, spin. You know what I'm saying?
Mike Sackton: And, and, like… Actually, let's just think about this for a little bit, like, who's, who's done the… who's been, like.
Mike Sackton: Rolling the worst.
Mike Sackton: And 9.
Tim Sackton: Me, I'm totally into the vibe here.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Esco's locked in.
Mike Sackton: Who of, who of the other, who of,
David S. Kong: Schwartz, Schwartz.
Mike Sackton: Little, little pony.
David S. Kong: Little Tony's got that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I got some I got some issues, sure. Yeah, you know.
Mike Sackton: I'm gonna, like, do a whole, like, like, little spiel, like, like, like, you know, here's how you… here's how you think about this the right way, like, give Little Tony a whole bunch.
David S. Kong: question.
Mike Sackton: Like, right? So in theory, you should get advantage on your next attempt.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I can also cast Enhance Ability.
Mike Sackton: I was saying that I could also cast enhanceability.
Tim Sackton: It gives you advantage for the next hour, that seems very useful.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, in this situation.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): that, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, I mean, sure. Why don't we get two enhanced abilities going?
David S. Kong: What level spell slot is this?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): second.
David S. Kong: Second, okay.
Mike Sackton: I'm… I'm just gonna… you know what? I'm just gonna say, like.
Mike Sackton: My ability here, like, it's just, like…
Mike Sackton: goes crazy, right? And way better than usual. And I'll just, it'll become enhanceability for you, little Toby.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And I'm gonna wait, you're casting it on me and I'm casting it on you or who's?
Mike Sackton: Or… or… Either me or,
Tim Sackton: You should cast it on… on… Zeno, because Zeno can…
Tim Sackton: Can use hype on somebody not.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, yeah, yeah, there we go. Well, so…
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes.
Mike Sackton: So Zena will hide look. We're a very cooperative bunch here.
Mike Sackton: Sculpet's making Little Tony better, Little Tony's making Zeno better, and Zeno's making Sculpet better.
Mike Sackton: No selfishness here, right? We're all like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nobody's…
David S. Kong: Drag it out.
Mike Sackton: Everybody's hyping somebody else up, that's how we.
David S. Kong: It's a hype train.
Eric Rosenbaum: Love it. Love it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Picture this shoulder massage circle.
Tim Sackton: Let's get walking!
Eric Rosenbaum: Wing missile.
Mike Sackton: Alright, let's try this again. We got this.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Is there a way to set the advantage directly on the roll?
Tim Sackton: If you right click, you can…
Tim Sackton: I don't know what you can say.
Mike Sackton: Roll with advantage.
Mike Sackton: Dude!
Eric Rosenbaum: Look at that!
Mike Sackton: Eric, what's your hype ability?
Eric Rosenbaum: Plus one D4.
Mike Sackton: Okay, so I just get plus 1D4.
Tim Sackton: That was not with Advantage.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, what is…
David S. Kong: So what are y'all trying to do now?
Tim Sackton: I got a 30.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): thing.
Eric Rosenbaum: if the…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Walking towards the beach.
David S. Kong: Walking towards the beach. Wait, you're at the beach. The beach is like behind you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, the walking into the water then.
David S. Kong: Walking into the water?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: We got a 20, a 30, a 25, and a whatever Zeno Eric won for Zeno.
Eric Rosenbaum: Why aren't my rules showing up in the thing?
Mike Sackton: Right click and say to, oops, ignore this.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Mike Sackton: You could say…
Eric Rosenbaum: Send to everyone is Seth.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, but the advantage thing didn't… Oh, that only works once.
Mike Sackton: advantage.
Mike Sackton: Or does it not stay?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I guess not.
Eric Rosenbaum: Anyways…
David S. Kong: What was that roll? Is there a way for me to see these?
Mike Sackton: Yeah, just in D&D Beyond.
David S. Kong: I'm in D&D Beyond.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Open up.
Tim Sackton: Gmail.
Mike Sackton: If you click on the game log.
David S. Kong: Where is that?
Eric Rosenbaum: Top right.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Top right.
Tim Sackton: Right next to where it says Campaign Dragonettes, there should be, like, click on anybody's character sheet, it doesn't matter.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Excellent.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wait, so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes.
Mike Sackton: Sorry, I accidentally rolled like 18 Arcana checks. My actual check was 25.
David S. Kong: Excellent.
Tim Sackton: Minus 30.
Eric Rosenbaum: you So mine are still not showing up, right? Alright, let me try this again…
Eric Rosenbaum: Roll send to everyone, roll the advantage… 18…
Mike Sackton: Yeah, that's weird, yours are not showing up.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'll reload, maybe?
Eric Rosenbaum: No VTT found that matches your settings.
Tim Sackton: Oh.
Mike Sackton: You have to turn off D&DB.
Tim Sackton: Disable, disable.
Tim Sackton: Disable the Beyond 20 plugin, that'll make it work much better.
Tim Sackton: Because that whole thing to send it to Roll20, now that D&D Beyond has its own virtual tabletop, it just adds a whole bunch of hassle.
David S. Kong: This particular thing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 3 out of 4, so…
Eric Rosenbaum: remove.
David S. Kong: You're probably kind of figuring out this mechanic. If you… if… if…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All four of you are successful, it's, like, extremely… it's, like, perfect.
David S. Kong: Three of you are successful, it's, like, mostly works. Two of you…
David S. Kong: And so on. Yeah. So, you got 3 out of 4 right now, so… you, you, the Wanderer…
David S. Kong: And this is like there are dragonets. Oh, because you can see.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: So, okay.
David S. Kong: Roska, Oru, like, and a whole bunch of other Dragonets are, like, they're, they're, like, there's fucking, like, a ton of Dragonets all, like, nearby, just, like, hovering, like, flying around.
David S. Kong: And they're buzzing by the head, like, you're inside the chest, you know what I mean? So you can't… there's no windows outside of his chest. But you can see that there's, like.
David S. Kong: Like, everybody is losing their shit. Like, that the Wanderer is… Like, this is… this is the craziest, craziest moment.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Recorded, memorized, you know, remembered history of Dragonets, the fact that all this shit is happening right now and the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: Raises his right leg, takes a step forward.
David S. Kong: Raises its left leg, takes another step forward.
David S. Kong: And that second step, Like, actually splashes into…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The beach.
David S. Kong: And, like, lands down, and the foot just, like, squishes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you feel…
David S. Kong: It's crazy, like, you're in it, you're sitting in the cockpit but your kind of talons in your feet, like, feel a little, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The sensation of being wet.
David S. Kong: And like.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The squishy rockiness of the edge of the beach, like, it's like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Holy You…
David S. Kong: actually.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: can feel… The Wanderer's first ever step.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, should we wander a little bit, you guys?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: All right.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Get out there.
Eric Rosenbaum: Other foot, go.
David S. Kong: So just, you don't have to do like foot by foot. Like, what are you guys trying to do? Like this next little, little, little step.
Tim Sackton: We're trying to watch…
David S. Kong: Oh, don't roll yet. Don't roll yet.
Tim Sackton: Oh, okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let's walk to like straight out till we're like waist deep, let's say.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, I was thinking… Sure, let's walk till we're wasting.
David S. Kong: Everybody's agreed, walked away.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: And now everybody roll.
Tim Sackton: 23.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 23.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Mike Sackton: 30.
David S. Kong: Oh, nice. Oh, wow.
Eric Rosenbaum: What just happened? Oh, I see, that was that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Ash.
David S. Kong: Eric, would you roll?
Eric Rosenbaum: And now… I'm so confused.
Eric Rosenbaum: So I turn off that extension.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm just gonna reload… oh, I had to reload the page again, probably.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: All right, now it's going to work. Roll the vintage.
Eric Rosenbaum: No, but now… you.
Tim Sackton: Oh, you probably… nope, there.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: How do I tell if the advantage thing worked?
Tim Sackton: That didn't meet you guys.
Eric Rosenbaum: It only rolled one.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, you just click it twice.
Eric Rosenbaum: And.
David S. Kong: So, so, so what did you roll, Eric?
Mike Sackton: It was at least a 27.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: 27.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, all right. So you, I mean, it's happening. The Wanderer takes the first step.
David S. Kong: And then another step.
David S. Kong: And another step. And there's, you know, the dragonets, there's, like, buzzing all around you. Tony, you can't… I mean, all of your concentration… and Tony, you find that this requires all of your concentration. You can't, like, just, like, start doing your, like, expanding your… while you're doing this. But!
David S. Kong: Even with the fact that you're fully focused and really need to fully focus on, on making the wanderer walk.
David S. Kong: You just get just larger vibes, it's sort of like the hair standing up on your, on your, you know, on your, your skin type of thing, like, everybody, all of the dragonets are like, holy the wanderer is, like, walking into the ocean, like, everybody is like, is like, like, holy this is actually happening.
David S. Kong: And so as you continue to take steps into the ocean.
David S. Kong: Well, I'm gonna kind of just, just, speed up this part a little bit. What other things are you trying to make the Wanderer do?
David S. Kong: In this little… next little period, over the next, like, half hour. You know, what other things are you…
Mike Sackton: I think we should, like, try and…
Mike Sackton: bend over and see if we can like pick up something from the ocean.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, I want to put the head in the water and see if we can look around underwater.
Tim Sackton: I like that.
David S. Kong: Give me, give me your, give me just collectively as a group right now, give me, give me, just give me a few, like, 3 things that you wanna, you wanna make sure you're doing. So, you wanna put your head in, you wanna look around, what else are you guys trying to do?
Mike Sackton: Pick up something like pick up some water or a rock or something from under the water.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Shipwreck would be awesome.
Mike Sackton: Really?
Eric Rosenbaum: just, like…
Mike Sackton: out.
Eric Rosenbaum: pick.
Mike Sackton: Good luck.
Tim Sackton: Whatever's on the bottom. All right, let's do that first.
Eric Rosenbaum: Some seabed yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, okay, try to scoop up some seabed. Yeah, everybody roll.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: 25.
David S. Kong: You guys are rolling so well.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 24.
Mike Sackton: 20… 3.
David S. Kong: Why are you all rolling so well? I gotta make this harder. All right, well, you.
Mike Sackton: It's okay if we just succeed, you know.
Tim Sackton: You made us level 10.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: We're all good at times.
David S. Kong: But no, we imposed ourselves. It's amazing. Well, part of this also just like, let's just roll out. Like you all feel locked in. You feel like, holy shit.
David S. Kong: like, this is a massive, unimaginably massive fucking statue, and it's feeling… it's starting to feel like, just as you kind of experiment and do stuff, it's feeling more and more comfortable. Yeah, like, you're able to reach down, you pull out, like, a giant, like.
David S. Kong: You know, massive fucking volume of, like, rock and sand from the… from the bottom, and… and it kind of crumbles down between your fingers down and smashing into the ocean, like, all the fucking rocks and things, like, just, like, landing and smashing.
David S. Kong: What else do you try to do? Just, like, two more things that are, like, just whatever you want to do in the statue. And guys, this is…
Mike Sackton: And underwater, right?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, stick our head underwater.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): for sure.
David S. Kong: Okay, and try to look around? Yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: Alright, go ahead, roll.
Tim Sackton: That would be another 23.
Mike Sackton: Quarterly… and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 20.
Mike Sackton: 29.
David S. Kong: Okay. Yeah, you put your head under the water.
David S. Kong: And you can indeed see.
Mike Sackton: So, while our head's underwater, can we try and blow bubbles?
Eric Rosenbaum: Is that gonna work? I don't know.
Mike Sackton: Oh, What happens when we, like, open our mouth and… Is there anything?
Eric Rosenbaum: intense.
Mike Sackton: Can we, like, blow out? Like, is there any source of… Voted forced to…
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe we should open the mouse.
Eric Rosenbaum: Out of the water.
David S. Kong: The food.
Eric Rosenbaum: Sure, we can.
Tim Sackton: Oh, that's way too obvious!
David S. Kong: True.
Eric Rosenbaum: Fair, fair.
Mike Sackton: I mean, we're really doing well with this, like, let's just… let's just…
David S. Kong: Decide two more things. So what are the two more things that you're going to do?
Eric Rosenbaum: I guess we're blowing bubbles.
Tim Sackton: Blowing bubbles.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Tim Sackton: And… I don't know.
Mike Sackton: Can we, like, throw something?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, let's see how far let's let's pick.
Tim Sackton: See how far we can throw something like towards the storm, not.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, like, try to pick something up between two fingers.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like grab a rock. No, we'll try to pinch a seabird like a seagull out of the air.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe they clapped.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Don't look, Glenda. Don't look.
David S. Kong: So what are you trying to do?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think we should pick up like pick up a big boulder and see if we can throw it all the way to the storm.
David S. Kong: Cool.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, I'm with that. Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, that is actually a better idea than my seagull squashing idea.
David S. Kong: Let's do the first part, which is picking up the boulder.
Tim Sackton: 99…
Eric Rosenbaum: I really want my advantage.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 20.
Eric Rosenbaum: work.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): For…
David S. Kong: Heska, you're 29?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: 20.
David S. Kong: Wow. Okay. So, okay. And, you know, just, you all are so lucky to have a fucking invincible rogue on your team as the lead acrobat for this fucking wonder.
Eric Rosenbaum: Whoa.
David S. Kong: successful.
Tim Sackton: Just testing. That wasn't a real role.
David S. Kong: You.
Eric Rosenbaum: The advantage thing just does not work, I don't know why.
Mike Sackton: I've deemed the odds as bad.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, but you have… you can't… if you click Advantage and then click away from the menu, it won't roll. You have to click the little button that says Roll.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, That'll work next time, okay.
Tim Sackton: That's what I was just testing.
Tim Sackton: Now everybody's dice are spawning.
Tim Sackton: Okay, let Concal's laugh. Yeah, yeah.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay. Wait, so, but everybody rolled over 20 on that last one.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, so all of you, you successfully pick up the boulder, you successfully pick up the rock, and then Heska.
David S. Kong: You know, again, part of what's happening here, and part of why you're rolling the way it's that you're rolling, okay?
David S. Kong: As you're, you know, over the course of this now, you know, this is, like, now, like, at least an hour, you know, or so, that you've been just doing all of this, talking, experimenting, and so on.
David S. Kong: What you're starting to appreciate about how you're actually controlling this whole thing.
David S. Kong: Tony, you're having this insight into, like, I have this thing that we collectively want to do and is this, like, thought about what it is that you're trying to do.
David S. Kong: translating into the system, this whole giant mechanical system. It's like, you're almost, like, kind of helping this coordination around
David S. Kong: Like the connection between the idea and then the translation into the format itself at all, and it's almost like if your shit doesn't work, it's like everybody could be like, let's fucking do this thing, and then the whole system is just getting weird, confused messages about, like, what to do.
David S. Kong: Heska, you're starting to feel like if all of the other systems are like aligned and rock and roll, it's like the physical attributes of what's happening with the system.
David S. Kong: It's like if everything else is locked in, it's like you are actually the wanderer. It's like you are able to like throw shit and you're Heska now 10th level and it's like, oh fuck. Like it's an insane like as crazy as this day is felt and how you have personally felt about yourself.
David S. Kong: The fact that you now almost feel like you've got this like fucking massive hundreds of feet tall avatar that is like.
David S. Kong: Approximating some level of, like, what you feel like you can do.
David S. Kong: You process that however you want to process that.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it for you. There's like kind of a a multi-dimensional of like
David S. Kong: like, this feeling of, like, power around what it is that is actually happening with the system. It's almost like if, like, you are rolling well, it's like the system is achieving its potential, like, in whatever it is. It's like, if you're really, really well, it's like, oh, fuck, like, I want to throw the boulder, you're gonna be able to throw that as far as you can, and just whatever is within your.
David S. Kong: possibility, you can achieve it. And you're like, you're there kind of almost expanding what is possible and helping the whole system like achieve what is possible.
David S. Kong: And then Xena…
David S. Kong: for you, this is also performance. This is this incredible orchestration, not only of all of you together, like, orchestrating these different kind of parts of the thing.
David S. Kong: But much like in musical performance and as you are like a conductor, there is another kind of harmony, harmony of all of the parts that you are bringing in. And if you, your shit does not work well, it's like having cool, like a really strong throw, but then like not having the, it's like, it's like you're, you're, you're, you're the, you're the overall conductor of the harmony of the entire system and making the whole system function together.
David S. Kong: So, you're all kind of realizing, you know, the different ways that you're contributing to this and how if all of you are super aligned.
David S. Kong: The statue is really doing what you want to do, and if
David S. Kong: one of you doesn't fail, multiple of you fails, it's… it's not gonna work. But, you know, it's pretty fortunate that Heska is on your team, because now it's like, you're kind of not… never, like, doing anything totally poorly, but, but it's pretty sweet. Like, you're all, like, really, really enjoying this time.
David S. Kong: And as you're experimenting and you're feeling, you know, and you're pretty lost in this kind of experiment.
David S. Kong: Tony, in between one of the breaks of as you're, like, doing this practice with the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: You feel a voice very clearly in your head.
David S. Kong: And it is Shaman Oru.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: like.
David S. Kong: Doing some shaman Uru shit, cause as, you know, as funny of a dude as he is, he also is like the eldest dragonet shaman and the most mystical dude on the island.
David S. Kong: And you get a message in your head that's basically like, Tony?
David S. Kong: Bring the others.
David S. Kong: Come to the Dark Lady.
David S. Kong: Something has come out of the sky.
David S. Kong: And it's crashed here.
David S. Kong: And… You should come and meet us to figure out what is going on.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
Tim Sackton: Let's, let's statue jog.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: You wanna go over as the statue?
Tim Sackton: Oh, yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: How far is it? I mean…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What a absurd question.
David S. Kong: So the lady and the wanderer are actually adjacent statues on the wheel around the island. So, okay, yeah, you can… well, roll some dice, see how well you get over there.
Tim Sackton: 23.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 15.
Mike Sackton: Oh, no.
Eric Rosenbaum: Summit.
Mike Sackton: Errol the One.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Now we all roll badly.
Mike Sackton: But with… with my, like, pumping up from,
Mike Sackton: From Zeno, even rolling a 1, I still get a 15.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
Mike Sackton: 15's not that good, but, you know.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Well, as you all start trotting over, to the other, just down the beach, down the shore.
David S. Kong: And start making your way over.
David S. Kong: What has happened at some point over this past stretch, unbeknownst to you, Tony, you, you would have totally detected this, but you're spending all of your energy, piloting a giant, you know.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Ancient statue in the water and doing crazy shit.
David S. Kong: There was something else unfolding not far from you down the beach.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: There was a vessel.
David S. Kong: That it crashed.
David S. Kong: And two humanoid figures.
David S. Kong: That had emerged from the vessel.
David S. Kong: And… What had happened was, after they had emerged.
David S. Kong: They were undetected for a while.
David S. Kong: But then, soon, because, you know, there's a giant village, up over the cliff.
David S. Kong: Some dragonets saw that there were some two somethings down there, and dragonets also being dragonets, they flew down to go and greet the somethings.
David S. Kong: And as you all arrive.
David S. Kong: And I'm assuming you're, as you're kind of going down the beach, this, this scene is, is near the beach, so this is something that, you know, and you'll, you also see, like, there's, you know, because the dragonets are also kind of following you guys, there are waves of dragonets, like, near you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know.
David S. Kong: Landing on the statue, just like kind of pecking around and stuff.
David S. Kong: But you basically see this scene. It's now, you know, this is like hundreds of feet away from you, but with the wanderer's eyes, you can actually see this crash site. And you see these two figures.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: And there's like a handful of dragonettes that are talking. They're like all kind of animated. And you see a lot of animated like kind of like this and that, you know, with these figures.
David S. Kong: One of them is Shaman Oru, who's there. And you also see Roska there with a couple of his…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: His clansmen who are more like the bodyguards, you know, kind of more of the fighters.
David S. Kong: What do you do?
Tim Sackton: you
Tim Sackton: I'm not… I don't think Heska's really ready to get out of the statue. Can we, like, wave to them with the statue? Like, come over here? Can we try and talk as the statue?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Now that's an interesting idea. We should definitely try to talk as a statue. Yes. What are we going to say?
Tim Sackton: So I just think hello.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, let's think. Puny mortals, you have trespassed in our domain.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Explain your business or die!
Mike Sackton: No, let's stay.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Mike Sackton: It's us in here controlling this. Who are you?
Tim Sackton: No, no, no.
Tim Sackton: Hello!
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay, let's just do hello first and see what happens. But loud.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like a scary kind of hello. Like hello.
Tim Sackton: You can do a scary hello like hello.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tim Sackton: Has anything happened? Can we try it?
David S. Kong: Give it a shot.
Eric Rosenbaum: Get a roll, okay.
Tim Sackton: 29.
Mike Sackton: Oh.
Mike Sackton: It was a 20, and then it rolled over to a 2.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 24.
Eric Rosenbaum: too.
Tim Sackton: Got you.
Mike Sackton: Sculpet's heart really isn't in this.
Tim Sackton: you.
Mike Sackton: 13.
David S. Kong: And what are you trying to do again?
Mike Sackton: Shout out to Gary. Hello.
Tim Sackton: You say hello.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: In Dragonet tongue?
Tim Sackton: In like a spooky way.
David S. Kong: But in Dragonet language, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, so basically what happens is, yeah, like the statue like kind of goes.
David S. Kong: Yeah, perfect. It's making noises. Again, you kind of have…
David S. Kong: It, like, you feel like you're kind of saying something, but then you're kind of like realizing that maybe this thing wasn't designed totally to say stuff out loud, but.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's like…
David S. Kong: But, but you also feel like
David S. Kong: Like, maybe it could, but you're just not quite doing it right. But it's making a noise, it's going like…
David S. Kong: Like that.
David S. Kong: Tony, you hear a voice in your head again, and it's the shaman, and he's saying, Tony, get here now.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We're here! This is us, man!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What, what…
Tim Sackton: Can we at least wave?
David S. Kong: You can win.
Tim Sackton: Let's make it wave and say, like, make it do this, like, come here.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like.
David S. Kong: Coming into the ocean.
Tim Sackton: Like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): standing.
Tim Sackton: Sure.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, we're gonna walk… I think, like, we should walk over and, like, squat down next to him.
David S. Kong: And.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): the
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And then we can tell… we can tell the shaman that… that that's who we are, and we'll be like, I'm gonna… we'll do this, I'm gonna go… I'm gonna do a big pointy thing…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, that's perfect.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): For Tony.
Tim Sackton: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Even though we don't.
Eric Rosenbaum: That'll definitely… that'll definitely work.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you So what are you doing? What are you all doing?
Tim Sackton: Pointing at ourselves and making a tea.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We'll walk over and squat down next to everybody, Give a thumbs up, Sue.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, I think that.
Tim Sackton: Sky.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No.
David S. Kong: Okay, I mean, they're all, they're all looking at you, but
David S. Kong: Yeah, I mean, everybody's like, oh, shit, like, it's a giant fucking statue, like, doing a T and whatever, but, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): funny.
David S. Kong: And then Tony's, and then you hear a voice, Sean's like, we need to speak with you. Like, come.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh.
David S. Kong: with us.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, see, you need to be specific, Shaman. It's, you know, you know. Guys, we should probably go, guys.
Tim Sackton: Okay…
Tim Sackton: Let's go.
Eric Rosenbaum: You mean, like, park this thing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, let's stand it up back. We should stand it up back in its regular, like, in its handout.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, probably.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): for it to be like crouching, right?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: A little weird, yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, we should go over and it should like put its arm around the dark lady.
David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And be like, hey…
Eric Rosenbaum: You know what we should do? We should make him kind of cough and put the mouth up by the hand up by the mouth, and then we can like jump out the mouth into the hand and then it can like lower us down.
Eric Rosenbaum: You know what I'm saying?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): These are all really good ideas.
Eric Rosenbaum: I know.
David S. Kong: All right, so let's decide how you're exiting. Let's just… let's land up, let's…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Dragonets.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There was a sense of urgency to the request.
David S. Kong: Yes, yes. The sound is like in your ear, like, what the fuck, Tony, dude.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like.
David S. Kong: Come now.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: W- You're as bad as a cloud.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, let's just stand back up and leave it parked in the original position, right?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That sounds good, yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And then we'll come down.
Eric Rosenbaum: We'll do the coffee thing, right?
David S. Kong: And just just out of out of curiosity, like, do you flat of its eyeball? Do you teleport? Like, what's the the eyeball?
Tim Sackton: I'm just gonna fly out of its eyeball. Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, great. Yep, yep.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay, I guess so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: So every, you know, so you fly out of the eyeball and of course everybody like, you know, there are other dragonettes hanging out outside and you recognize some friends and some onlookers and everybody's just like, like all at once, like, what are you doing? You know, everybody's just trying to like, kind of talk to you guys about like, you know, what the hell's going on.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A bunch of people, dragonites start trying to fly into the eye.
David S. Kong: as you're exiting.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh guys, that's, that's, that's not gonna work. The stuff in there is gonna, it's gonna kill you. It's gonna, it's gonna zap them.
David S. Kong: Are you trying to stop anybody, or… Because they're actively dragging.
Mike Sackton: I will, like, shout, like, there's danger below!
David S. Kong: That doesn't matter, they're, they're, they're, they're trying to fly past you. Is it, are you trying to stop anybody or what's the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, I'll…
David S. Kong: There's like three dragonets that are trying to fly past you directly into the iris.
Mike Sackton: like use minor illusion to make a booming screaming voice of Sculpet saying
Mike Sackton: Listen, you will die if you go in there.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, tell me to ask Rosca about it.
David S. Kong: Two of them stopped, one of them is still trying to fly through.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna try and persuade the other one out of it.
David S. Kong: D20?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here goes, that's a 26.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What do you say? Like, no, the last guy who got in there, I barely got out with his life, and it was just, like, the laser shooting down, and the big giant statues, you know, be smart.
David S. Kong: 26. Even though you're kind of feel like you're babbling and saying a bunch of random stuff. Okay. It stops. Stops. It's like, okay. All right.
David S. Kong: And as you all fully kind of get within a certain radius away from the eyeball, it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let's look at it.
David S. Kong: Now what do you do?
Tim Sackton: I mean, the shaman wants to talk to us.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, let's,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Mike Sackton: school.
David S. Kong: approach the this this crash site and these you know and then there's basically as far as you can tell it feels like some kind of game of call and response is happening or it's like they're like a bunch of dragonites or like and then the two humanoids you don't sense at all that they're threatening in any way they're just kind of like they're they're engaging they're trying to like kind of understand each other and the shaman basically comes over and is like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, so,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The day gets, you know, the past couple days, as crazy as this has been, it's getting weirder, that thing fell out of the sky, and then, these 2,
David S. Kong: Humanoids that are like the statues, except way smaller.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, you know, like, I think we've had a little idea that there were maybe statue-sized things, but, like, not statue-sized things, like, kind of like the humanoids, but,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're trying to say stuff, we don't understand anything they're saying.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hmm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I don't know if you can help us, Tony, but…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There seems like a… this is… like, and basically, like, you kind of look over and realize the Dragonets are trying to play… it's like some version of charades, and they're trying to be like, you know, and there's kind of this, like, a bunch of, like, gesticulating back and forth, but there's no actual… that you can sense of it yet.
David S. Kong: You know, real communication happening.
David S. Kong: What do you do?
Tim Sackton: This is not my forte.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): More of a talk with everything.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Except for tiny living statues thing.
David S. Kong: Tony, remember, you kind of have the ability to just create telepathic connections.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, okay, I'll give that a shot.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I will come over, and I will say… Like, in…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): In very simple draconic, like, hello, me, Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You?
David S. Kong: And you're, you're communicating this telepathically?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yep.
David S. Kong: You see both of the humanoids kind of like look up and they're like, You, Tony?
David S. Kong: In your mind.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You?
David S. Kong: And then one of them points at themselves and says.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Shy. Guys, this one's shy. We should talk to the other one to keep this one feeling comfortable.
David S. Kong: And then the, the, the one that's like shy is like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Aksha.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Aksha.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Aksha. Okay, Aksha, Shai, we're getting somewhere.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let me level with you guys. It's been a weird-ass day. What are you doing here?
David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Why do you look like tiny little flesh versions of the statues?
David S. Kong: And you can see the humanoids, they're starting to like, they're talking to each other.
David S. Kong: Does anybody understand languages?
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't think so.
Mike Sackton: I don't think so.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Tony, you can roll an insight check and try to understand what they're saying. Like, you can, like, mediate the telepathy. And again, there's… you're able to, like, have this kind of, like, light communication, but roll an insight check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 17.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: You hear them saying to each other.
David S. Kong: I think this one is inside our minds.
David S. Kong: And I think it can understand what we're saying.
David S. Kong: And then the other one says, and this is like Shai talking to Aksha and Aksha's like.
David S. Kong: I think I feel it too. I wonder if we can… Get it to say.
David S. Kong: Hello again?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hello again?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll say.
David S. Kong: They both, like, Turn and snap their necks and look over.
David S. Kong: And for everybody else, again, it feels like this telepathic audience. It's like, you can kind of see… like, you're all in a room together, and it's like, you can see Tony talking to the two of them, and you're all kind of, like, watching.
David S. Kong: And you can all talk to Tony, but you can't necessarily talk to them. But it's kind of this like, but there is like a it's you're all starting to figure out how you might actually have a conversation now.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I said it is. I think they're sentient. They seem to be thinking and communicating on their own.
David S. Kong: The two humanoids, now that it feels, Like… Actually, it's possible to communicate.
David S. Kong: One of them…
David S. Kong: Basically, you sense and kind of can feel like just like a sense of like weeping and like relief. This is like one of the humanoids just starts like kind of shuddering, like crying. And then the other one's kind of like embracing it. And then.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, buddy, I'm gonna come over and try and give him a hug.
David S. Kong: the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna, like, walk over and, like, reach my arms out, like, come on, bring it in, bring it in.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Bring it in, guys, come on.
Eric Rosenbaum: Give him a comforting necklace.
David S. Kong: I'll just…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): back to the other three of you, like, come on, they need a hug. This clearly…
David S. Kong: It's been a hard day. They, they like collapse on the ground and both of them are just like weeping and like, you're, you're like literally like kind of group hugging them right now.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I'm just giving him a pat, like, oh, buddy, it's gonna be okay, it's gonna be okay.
David S. Kong: This is, this is, yeah, they are all…
David S. Kong: weeping and just, like, shaking. It's like… it's like they've been… it's like the best therapy session that you've ever had in your life.
David S. Kong: And they're experiencing, like, that breakthrough moment, where… and this is that moment for them, as they… as they are feeling your embrace and are.
David S. Kong: Moved. Moved beyond words.
David S. Kong: And as you, you know, kind of wrap up the group hug, and they all, they all sit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They…
David S. Kong: You see them kind of lift and pull their masks up.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: And you sit… Finally, to… Actually speak.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Aksha, who is the woman, and Shai, who's the guy with the beard and the top knot.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They…
David S. Kong: They look at…
David S. Kong: the four of you. They look at everybody and the four of you and the wanderer like crouched over and a st I mean.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they're… they're…
David S. Kong: Shai and Akshay, they both just say, you know.
David S. Kong: There are no words to describe what this means to be here.
David S. Kong: And to be with you.
David S. Kong: There's no words.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's really flattering. Thank you. I…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you know.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I…
David S. Kong: Everybody can communicate now, by the way. We're all, we kind of figured it out. You all know, figured out how to mediate through Tony to talk.
David S. Kong: None of the other diagnostics can do this, though.
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno's like… Peering around behind them at the strange glowing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Construction.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That seems to be their ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: He's…
David S. Kong: I'm like, I think we're…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll gesture to Zeno, he takes his time, he comes halfway closer and then halfway, it's sort of a.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A paradox.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno's Paradox.
David S. Kong: Ugh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'll get there, I'll get there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I mean…
David S. Kong: Wait, wasn't Zeno in the group hug?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Was Zeno in the group?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay. He's just joking about, you know… Getting halfway there.
David S. Kong: So.
David S. Kong: How is it possible that you're real?
Eric Rosenbaum: You're the ones… Who,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's a big question.
Eric Rosenbaum: Seem real to us.
Tim Sackton: Same, same, same.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Tim Sackton: Jessica will like.
Mike Sackton: What are you?
Tim Sackton: Over a little, like… Reach to, like…
Tim Sackton: Pinch one of them, just… and then, like, back off, because he's nervous.
David S. Kong: He, like, the, the, the… which one do you try to pinch?
Tim Sackton: The woman.
Tim Sackton: But I don't get too close.
David S. Kong: Make an acrobatics check. That's going to be insanely hard to do it anyways.
Tim Sackton: 27.
Mike Sackton: you.
David S. Kong: So, you successfully do it, but she also, like, and, like, grabs your claw, and it's just, like, just grabs it.
Tim Sackton: No, I don't get closer to more than, like, 5… I'm not getting within 5 feet of her.
David S. Kong: Oh.
Tim Sackton: I'm like moving forward like I'm gonna pinch her, but it's too scared to actually…
David S. Kong: Oh, I see, I see, I see. Okay, okay. Yeah, no, she just, she just, she just watches. And then, and then, you know, again, they kind of collect themselves again. And then they both like…
David S. Kong: Get down on their knees.
David S. Kong: And then they bow. They just, like… Like that. Like, reverently.
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna, like, look behind me, like, who they're bowing to.
David S. Kong: To you, to the four of you, like bowing, like reverently, reverently.
Eric Rosenbaum: I could get used to this, this is alright, yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This feels right.
Eric Rosenbaum: You're going to need.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): feels right.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're gonna need some wait staff at the restaurant, you know what I'm saying?
David S. Kong: What? Are you enslaving them? Is that what's happening? What?
Mike Sackton: Okay, wait, wait, I want to understand this. Let's go a couple of seconds.
Mike Sackton: Wait.
Mike Sackton: Where did you come from?
David S. Kong: Where did we come from?
David S. Kong: Have you ever left this place?
Mike Sackton: Of course not, there's nothing out there.
Eric Rosenbaum: What else is there?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wait, are you from…
Mike Sackton: Outside the storm?
David S. Kong: We are from outside the storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes!
Mike Sackton: I thought it was all just, Nothing.
Mike Sackton: Like, forever.
David S. Kong: It's a big storm.
David S. Kong: And, we didn't make it all the way through it, that's why we, I mean.
David S. Kong: The vessel's still functional, but we can…
David S. Kong: Probably get… we can get it working, but…
David S. Kong: I'm sure it still works, but that's part of why we crashed.
David S. Kong: Ashka's Incredible.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: pilot.
David S. Kong: That's how we were able to survive getting through here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But…
David S. Kong: Was not easy getting through that storm.
David S. Kong: But we had to, to come and find you.
Eric Rosenbaum: Why?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, why would you want to find us? Yeah. What?
Tim Sackton: There's nothing interesting about the island, really. I mean, there is, it's great, it's our home.
Mike Sackton: Wait, yeah, does… I mean, there's the performances, there's the, like, track… does…
Mike Sackton: Best singers and acrobats, like, there's a lot of interesting things.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There is gonna be a restaurant!
Tim Sackton: Oh, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: food machine.
Tim Sackton: In the hand?
Eric Rosenbaum: You just think of a foodie.
Tim Sackton: screen.
Tim Sackton: We can make a moving restaurant.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Awesome.
Tim Sackton: Assuming we can control any statue.
David S. Kong: To the extent that any of you are paying attention to the four of them.
David S. Kong: Like, to them. Like, the feeling you get is, like, this… on the one hand, this just, like, hilarious, like, what are these beings?
David S. Kong: What are they talking about? They're so funny, they're so weird. And then at the same time, like the deepest possible sorrow that you can imagine, like so deep and so sorrowful. You don't even relate to the sorrow, obviously, as dragonettes and the lives that you've had.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's.
David S. Kong: Almost like this feeling of.
David S. Kong: I understand conceptually these things you're describing, but I have never experienced them ever in my entire life.
Mike Sackton: So wait, what, what, what are, like, What?
Mike Sackton: What are you?
Eric Rosenbaum: Use your wings somehow?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): and get all weird looking.
Mike Sackton: Like, are you guys gods?
Mike Sackton: That's what the statues are, right?
David S. Kong: At that, at that, Shai just like starts laughing hilariously. Are we gods?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You ask?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You, the firstborn, ask if we are gods?
Mike Sackton: I wasn't born first.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: No, I wasn't either.
Mike Sackton: talking about it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Who was born first?
Eric Rosenbaum: Shannon.
David S. Kong: Shai and Akshar are just like staring at each other, just like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
David S. Kong: incredulous.
Mike Sackton: Bye.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Bye.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Howie, were you here when the clutch hatched?
Mike Sackton: Why would you say such silly things?
Mike Sackton: Are you okay? Are you, like, addled a little bit?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Beseth.
David S. Kong: the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Race? Like everyone hatches when it's time to hatch, man!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What happened… Like, 2 days ago. Did anything happen here on this island?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Have you always…
David S. Kong: Was this statue always able to walk? Were you…
Tim Sackton: So absolutely nothing at all happened two days ago. Everybody forget that that day occurred.
Tim Sackton: Heska will say emphatically.
Eric Rosenbaum: What do you mean?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yo, two days ago, the most.
Eric Rosenbaum: I've.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): incredible thing happen you've ever.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There was this competition.
Tim Sackton: No, I said.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It was quite good, but it was… it was really… so you have to meet, Xena, right? Like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, he kind of had to be there.
Mike Sackton: Kind of had to be there, like, none of us were there. Well, I mean, I was there, but none of the rest of us were…
Eric Rosenbaum: But I.
Mike Sackton: Haskell.
Eric Rosenbaum: Finally…
Mike Sackton: Don't, don't worry about it. He doesn't want you to, we just, right.
Eric Rosenbaum: I finally beat Rosca.
Mike Sackton: Gotcha.
Eric Rosenbaum: In a battle, you know what I'm saying?
David S. Kong: Roscoe.
Mike Sackton: think.
David S. Kong: behind you and it's just like looks like annoyed like he's just like dude kind of like what's.
Mike Sackton: guys.
Eric Rosenbaum: I just squashed him like a bug. Wait, I…
Mike Sackton: I think they're probably talking about…
Eric Rosenbaum: him under the rug.
Mike Sackton: Ag?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Mike Sackton: Agri.
Tim Sackton: Oh…
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What?
Mike Sackton: I know that, like, the competition's more important, like, the…
Mike Sackton: I mean, the restaurant, there's a lot of…
Eric Rosenbaum: You can reenact it if you want.
Mike Sackton: The egg is very minor, but.
David S. Kong: Reenacting? Yeah, please. What happened? Can you do the reenactment?
Eric Rosenbaum: The Rosca and my battle. Yeah, we could just like.
David S. Kong: No, no, not that, not that. Reenacting the whatever he's pointing at at Sculpit. Reenacting what? What happened?
Mike Sackton: Here we go, okay. I know how to do this now.
Mike Sackton: Skullbit will use Bire Illusion to.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: Cool, cool.
Mike Sackton: like, a little picture of an egg, and then, like, he… he's still learning how to use minor illusions, so he does, like, do-do-do side effects with his voice, not realizing he can do them with the illusion. And then he, like, changes the illusion again to, like, the next bit.
Mike Sackton: this… this is what happened. And then… and then we all sit around, and it was really… it was really nice, and like… and like, we were very connected.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Mike Sackton: And then we woke up and we, like, started thinking about the restaurant, but mostly these guys. I don't think the restaurant's as good an idea as they do. So, like, that kind of… that kind of, like.
Mike Sackton: Broke some of the, like.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: There's a little…
David S. Kong: Yeah, we understand the restaurant, maybe let's… we'll come back to the restaurant. What happened?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We'll come back to the restaurant. That's it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: we.
David S. Kong: I'm.
Tim Sackton: I mean, a restaurant only works with repeat customers, right?
David S. Kong: Very hungry.
Mike Sackton: It could be, like, a tourist trap restaurant that, like… like…
Mike Sackton: Okay, maybe if more of these people come from…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Press in recorded history. That's true.
Tim Sackton: This trap restaurant is not gonna work.
Eric Rosenbaum: - no, no, no.
Mike Sackton: Guys, guys, guys, I'm trying to be serious, okay, shh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Focus, we gotta focus, focus.
Mike Sackton: Okay, so there was this Ken.
Mike Sackton: And Sculpin will make a picture of the egg, right? And, like, we had this…
David S. Kong: the.
Mike Sackton: vision.
David S. Kong: from?
Mike Sackton: It, like… Neat.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sky. Stop it.
Mike Sackton: there, somewhere?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Tim Sackton: space.
Mike Sackton: But there was like…
Eric Rosenbaum: It disappeared in the hand, didn't it?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, that's why it's worth 2 in the bush.
Mike Sackton: It floated.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh!
Mike Sackton: Sort of.
Eric Rosenbaum: minutes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Did it?
Mike Sackton: I like that.
Tim Sackton: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Kind of, like, hovered?
Mike Sackton: It, it, like, appeared somehow.
David S. Kong: What happened? What did you do to the egg? What did you do with the egg?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Man, the same thing we just did to you.
Mike Sackton: We told it about the restaurant.
David S. Kong: No, we gave it a good look.
Tim Sackton: We gave it a hug.
David S. Kong: Wait.
Mike Sackton: And it must have heard about the restaurant, because the next day, it made food everywhere.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is actually a really good point.
Eric Rosenbaum: as.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: And we should follow up on that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh!
David S. Kong: But then you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He wants us to have an omelet restaurant.
Mike Sackton: But so there was like a creature like like
Mike Sackton: like a Dragonette like one of us who was like dead or dying or something like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sad, like your vibes, yeah.
Mike Sackton: Like a red sky everywhere and like some hand like.
David S. Kong: Die everywhere.
Mike Sackton: Wasn't it, like, somebody's, like, broken hand, or dead hand, or cut-off hand, or something like that?
Tim Sackton: Oh, weird green.
Mike Sackton: It was like a jade hand, like a hand of gemstones.
Tim Sackton: It was stone.
Mike Sackton: So, greenstone, a greenstone hand.
David S. Kong: By the way, the vision was just the scratching part. That was the part where the dragonet was thinking about home.
Mike Sackton: Okay.
David S. Kong: All the things that felt like home for it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right.
David S. Kong: Huh. And then… and then what happened?
Mike Sackton: We.
Eric Rosenbaum: We'll have enough of that.
Mike Sackton: We woke up.
Tim Sackton: And then we were hungry and then we ate some food. Okay. And the food.
Mike Sackton: Came out of the bathroom.
David S. Kong: Wait, hold on, wait, wait. I just, I know you, I'm starting to understand you love the food. This is, this is bad. Akshay, the woman's like leading the conversation. She's like, okay, no, no. So you understand, I think we understand. And he's like, she's looking at Shai. We're excited about the restaurant. We can't wait to eat at the restaurant.
David S. Kong: But before we talk more about the restaurant.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
David S. Kong: Say more about how you got the giant statue to move and do the things that it was doing earlier, just now.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute. It's an exchange of information.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Why.
Tim Sackton: What can we tell you? What if you want to take the statue?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah!
Tim Sackton: Our statue.
David S. Kong: exactly.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Exactly right, we took it already.
Mike Sackton: Wait, aren't there, like, 8 of them?
Mike Sackton: My friend…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Jimmy the Squid says never give anything away without getting something in return. So what you tell us what your deal is.
David S. Kong: We're here to find you.
Mike Sackton: Hmm?
Tim Sackton: Why?
Mike Sackton: Did you hear about the restaurant?
Eric Rosenbaum: Probably.
David S. Kong: Laughing.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: You could say that.
David S. Kong: We're very hungry.
David S. Kong: I, I maybe to say it another way,
David S. Kong: And they both get really emotional, like… you don't know…
David S. Kong: Or maybe you do know how lucky you are.
David S. Kong: Have what you have here.
David S. Kong: This is, this is incredible.
David S. Kong: This is an incredible place. Y'all are incredible.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's… what's it like where you're from?
David S. Kong: It's not like this.
Tim Sackton: mean.
David S. Kong: Imagine is the opposite of this.
Tim Sackton: You could… You could probably stay, right? We can let them stay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah!
David S. Kong: So kind of like.
David S. Kong: They both just are so, like, moved, like,
David S. Kong: You would let us stay here.
Tim Sackton: Why not?
Mike Sackton: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: They both start kind of weeping again.
David S. Kong: There are others like us.
David S. Kong: Would they be able to come?
Mike Sackton: I I mean, there's a lot of…
Tim Sackton: A lot of space.
Mike Sackton: Sculp is kind of, like, looking at their size. I mean, like. How, how, like… Sure! We have plenty of space!
Tim Sackton: Can any of them… can they fish?
David S. Kong: One of them laughs.
David S. Kong: Can they fish? We could learn.
Mike Sackton: Maybe we could get the food thingy working again.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: They're just like.
David S. Kong: This is… They're, like, looking at each other's…
David S. Kong: Are we gonna work in their restaurant? And they both just, like, started laughing.
Mike Sackton: To be honest, guys, they need some good help.
Eric Rosenbaum: They're just like…
David S. Kong: You… you all don't understand What this means… What this all means.
David S. Kong: You're so generous, and you're so kind.
David S. Kong: You don't even know that you are and whatever it is that you think you're offering.
David S. Kong: The world needs it so badly, you don't even understand.
David S. Kong: What it's like out there.
David S. Kong: This place is a holy place.
David S. Kong: This is Holy Land.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): we… We are pretty great. I think that's…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think it's remarkable how quickly you've settled on the essence of.
Mike Sackton: Is it like a storm all the way up there? Is that why it's so bad?
Mike Sackton: It's just stormy.
David S. Kong: But.
Mike Sackton: What's it like?
David S. Kong: Honestly?
David S. Kong: The feeling that… I have right now, that we have being here with you all.
David S. Kong: I don't know if we've ever felt this in our lives.
David S. Kong: This feeling of lightness and
David S. Kong: Joy, I mean, we feel it, we still feel it, we make it, we make do with it when we can.
David S. Kong: But life out there.
David S. Kong: It's hard.
David S. Kong: It's really hard.
David S. Kong: And you look at them, and just kind of stepping back a little bit, and you're like.
David S. Kong: You've never seen humans before, obviously, but They are beat the up.
David S. Kong: Like, they look like they have been through some serious
David S. Kong: I mean, this doesn't show in here, but, you know, they are beaten down, scarred, dirty.
David S. Kong: Just whatever they have been through, it is, it is, it's, it looks like they've had it.
Mike Sackton: You know, the water's pretty nice. Maybe you should, like.
Mike Sackton: Take a bath, and, like, get some new clothes, and, like, relax a little bit, and then maybe you can…
Mike Sackton: See how you can get more of your friends to come here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's like, I don't know how to say this politely, but like, you look…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's the right word to say? Bad. Like, really. Like, not.
Mike Sackton: That… Tony, Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Not good.
Mike Sackton: Tony.
Tim Sackton: They.
Mike Sackton: that.
Tim Sackton: I mean, they've had a hard…
Mike Sackton: That wasn't the right choice.
Tim Sackton: Road crashed.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Are they supposed to smell like that though?
Eric Rosenbaum: We're not supposed to smell shit.
Tim Sackton: Who knows what they're supposed to…
David S. Kong: We're not supposed.
Tim Sackton: We… how do you know what we smell like to them?
Mike Sackton: Probably fish. The best smell in the world.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's right. You do.
David S. Kong: You smell like fish. You do smell like fish.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hmm.
David S. Kong: We like fish. I mean, it's impossible to get, but…
Mike Sackton: So, Wait, why is fish… wait, what? There's no fish out there?
Mike Sackton: you.
David S. Kong: I mean, some people get to eat fish, but not us.
Mike Sackton: What do you mean?
David S. Kong: What do we eat? Not fish. I'll tell you that much. It's been a long time since I've tasted fish.
Mike Sackton: Do you eat that weird stringy stuff that looks like hair?
Tim Sackton: The metal… Squiggles? Nobody could eat the metal squiggles.
Mike Sackton: all.
Eric Rosenbaum: No, the other stuff.
Mike Sackton: Not the metal ones, the booty.
Tim Sackton: Gloopy ones.
Mike Sackton: The gloopy ones.
David S. Kong: They suddenly kind of get serious as they're looking at each other. Like, listen.
David S. Kong: We may not have a lot of time.
David S. Kong: I don't know how this all happened.
David S. Kong: How we've all been able to meet.
David S. Kong: But we're so grateful.
David S. Kong: To be in your presence.
David S. Kong: Whatever's happened to you the past few days, It doesn't matter anymore.
David S. Kong: What we know now, Is that… you're here?
David S. Kong: You've been touched by the gods.
David S. Kong: And now… everything is different.
David S. Kong: But we're not alone.
David S. Kong: And… Now, this place, this holy place, That…
David S. Kong: I can't even put into words.
David S. Kong: It must be protected at all costs.
Eric Rosenbaum: because.
David S. Kong: there's That are coming.
David S. Kong: To find this place.
David S. Kong: Terrible.
David S. Kong: terrible beings.
David S. Kong: Are gonna come and find this place.
Mike Sackton: Hmm.
Tim Sackton: Mmm…
David S. Kong: Have a lot of time.
Tim Sackton: They've never before.
Eric Rosenbaum: Terrible.
Tim Sackton: That's a good sound.
David S. Kong: The both of them start, like, looking, like, really nervous.
David S. Kong: We're forgetting ourselves. Go get the scanner.
David S. Kong: Shy, like, runs back into the ship.
David S. Kong: And, he comes back out with, like, a device Some kind.
David S. Kong: And they both start.
David S. Kong: looking at this…
David S. Kong: This system, it's, it's hard, I mean, again, you never see, it's like, you just have it, like, this reminds you of something that you might have seen inside the, inside the, the cockpit of the, the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: And they look… And their faces go, just… Blank white.
David S. Kong: Like, complete terror and horror on their faces as they look at each other.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: All of you need to hide. You need to get all of your people and hide now. There's no more time. You must hide now.
David S. Kong: They're coming.
Mike Sackton: What's going?
Tim Sackton: What's coming, and what have you done to our nice island?
David S. Kong: We have done nothing.
David S. Kong: Your presence, you've awakened. They're coming now.
David S. Kong: Get everyone to safety NOW.
Eric Rosenbaum: Should we all? Should we all go in the statue?
Mike Sackton: Who's they? More like you?
David S. Kong: Not like us.
Mike Sackton: Are they big or little? Can you give us one piece of information?
David S. Kong: They start talking to each other.
David S. Kong: It wasn't tracking us. They must have found the signatures themselves.
David S. Kong: They're gonna be here soon.
David S. Kong: How long do we have?
David S. Kong: Not long.
David S. Kong: 5 minutes, 10 minutes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): All right, I'll say to our shaman friend, everyone's got to hide.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): For unclear reasons.
David S. Kong: The shaman's like, what? Why are we hiding? Is this the game?
David S. Kong: Is this the game?
Tim Sackton: We don't know. Something about these…
David S. Kong: The two of them.
Tim Sackton: Cheers!
David S. Kong: Like, they're like, look, We don't know exactly what's coming.
David S. Kong: It's gonna come. I think they're gonna breach the storm. We need to be ready. Everyone needs to go to safety. We're gonna try and do our best to fight it off the best that we can. We need your help. If you can… whatever you can do, but make sure everyone is safe. This is…
David S. Kong: you don't understand the danger that's coming, and it's hard to describe it, but just… everybody needs to hide, you need to get everyone to safety now. There's no time. And you sense… the gravity and the urgency. This is not a game. The few kind of sacred, serious things that have ever happened in Dragonet history, of which there are very few.
David S. Kong: You feel like this is one where
David S. Kong: If you don't do this the right way, there will be death.
David S. Kong: there will be… Clutchlings… Eggs. This… something as horrible is gonna happen.
David S. Kong: What do you do?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): How do we get everyone hidden to safety?
David S. Kong: The shaman comes over. What's happening?
Mike Sackton: It sounds like some bad thing is happening. We gotta, like,
Mike Sackton: Get everybody to hide, I guess?
David S. Kong: Well.
David S. Kong: And the best place to hide is the temple.
David S. Kong: Do we need to get everybody to the temple?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Oh.
David S. Kong: Are you, is this serious?
Mike Sackton: I think so.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sure sounds like it.
David S. Kong: The shaman looks…
David S. Kong: Raska, tell the others, get everybody to hide. Move to the temple now. Is this for real? Now?
Eric Rosenbaum: So Kong, the temple is the dead center of the island or where?
David S. Kong: Dead center of the island. But it's like a structure. Everything else, Dragon Island is just, you're all living like outside.
Eric Rosenbaum: Mmm.
David S. Kong: you know.
Eric Rosenbaum: The Groundlings Cave, that monastery.
Eric Rosenbaum: That I remember from childhood.
David S. Kong: Okay, that's a good place.
Eric Rosenbaum: newsletter.
David S. Kong: the.
Eric Rosenbaum: underground.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Underground complex, yeah, it's not huge, but…
David S. Kong: Okay, that'll fit, that'll fit some. Good.
David S. Kong: Are you saying that out loud to the shaman? That's, like, a suggestion?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Shaman.
David S. Kong: The shaman turns to Raska. Get as many as you can into the temple, get as many as you can underground.
David S. Kong: A dire emergency. Let's… let's go.
David S. Kong: And Rosca, I mean, this is like
David S. Kong: Dragonets being serious, like, this shit never happens, and this is like a, like, but a feeling like, okay, let's, let's do what we gotta do.
David S. Kong: And Rosca and, there's a flurry of action and people start, but it's, it's also like, is this a game or like, everybody is trying to figure out like, is this serious? Is it not serious? You know?
David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Meanwhile.
David S. Kong: You find, Tony, that you're able to maintain this telepathic connection with Shai and with Aksha? Like, everybody, they're all kind of in the link now with you all, and they're all able to communicate, at least for now?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they get back into their craft.
David S. Kong: And they say,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Good.
David S. Kong: Can you make that statue move again?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sure.
Mike Sackton: white.
David S. Kong: It's coming through the storm.
David S. Kong: We can see it, it's coming through the storm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Would we go out to meet it with the statue?
Tim Sackton: What is coming and why?
David S. Kong: As you all… Shai and Aksha have rushed back into.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: the,
David S. Kong: The ship.
David S. Kong: Are you all… what are the four of you doing?
David S. Kong: The other dragonets are scattering. They're starting to, you know.
Eric Rosenbaum: Back to the statue.
David S. Kong: You're flying back to the statue?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sure.
David S. Kong: As you… Start to fly back to the statue.
David S. Kong: You see…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: something… emerging from The storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's honestly indescribable to you in… Its size…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And the energy that it is emanating, which Reminds you of that vision.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of a place of no hope. Something full of despair.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And terror.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And horror.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you see emerging through the storm a massive.
Eric Rosenbaum: words.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You hear… Shy and Aksha's voices in your heads It's a fucking dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Are you inside the Wanderer?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Where are you?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sure, yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That makes sense.
David S. Kong: Role Initiative.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What is this gonna be?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh my god.
David S. Kong: Ahem.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, As you all… Get back into the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And settle into your cockpits.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: a massive… fucking… Ship has crashed through the storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: and A massive ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: also
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As flying out of it, a small group of smaller ships.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That power launching out of its… its bay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… bald now.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Are on this battlement.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How this is gonna work?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You all, are gonna roll individual initiative.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then… You all, instead of having a legendary action.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You all get a firstborn action.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Now… Your firstborn action.
David S. Kong: Should you choose to use it in this way.
David S. Kong: can be…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: a collective action for the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: So you get your individual action as your character.
David S. Kong: But then also you get to act as the wonderer.
David S. Kong: Now, you all know how to make the Wanderer move.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And do some basic you also discovered some things about the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: You remember Discovery Unlock.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You discovered that you could see out of the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: So there may be other things about the Wanderer you can discover as well if you try to do them.
Eric Rosenbaum: point.
David S. Kong: But you have to discover them successfully.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And all four of you, and again, this is the mechanic, you're rolling for against Insight, Performance, Arcana, Acrobatics.
David S. Kong: If all 4 of you act together and you succeed and you beat whatever the DC is, you are highly successful at whatever it is you're trying to do.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: If it's 3 of you succeed, 2 of you won, 0, then the success is proportional to how well you do.
David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, so all of you still have an individual action that you can do something that you want, but then you all, once per round, can make the Wanderer do something.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Whatever you want.
Mike Sackton: How big are the little ones flying around?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There's 4 of them, they're like the size of, they're like the size of, of Akshay and Shai's vessel.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you So, let's fucking do this shit. You ready to roll initiative?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, we already did. Okay, sorry, I missed it.
David S. Kong: I got a role in this dude.
David S. Kong: one second Oh, wait, how do I roll? Where? Oh, there's no list.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Just say them out loud for me. Sculpit, what's yours?
Mike Sackton: 16.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Pulpit and Zeno are both 16.
Tim Sackton: Pesca's 13, little Tony's 7.
David S. Kong: Little Tony's 7.
David S. Kong: Stop it.
David S. Kong: 16… Okay, and then… Give me one second here to roll for… This is… 14 and 17…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One more second…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 2, 6, and 8.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right, so the ship goes first, so Oxygen and Shy go first.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They fly over, and start attacking one of the ships, the smaller ships on the side.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they… Shoot an energy beam at it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they miss.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Up next, it is… Sculpt it.
David S. Kong: It's your turn.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How are you?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm just trying to figure out if these ships are…
Mike Sackton: Small enough, are they huge or smaller?
David S. Kong: Yeah, they're smaller than YouTube.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Right, okay. So I'm gonna summon, like, this huge…
Mike Sackton: hands.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay?
Mike Sackton: And it's gonna grab one of the ships.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: us.
Mike Sackton: One of the little shits.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: All right, what are you you're rolling an attack roll for it?
Mike Sackton: Big B's, it attempts to, let's see, the target must succeed on a deck saving throw.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Deck saving throw? Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's good.
David S. Kong: What spell is this?
Mike Sackton: Digby's Grasping Hand, so it's like the storm, right? Like the vibe, the flavor here is the storm, so it's like wind.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, like… And… Perfect. Perfect.
Mike Sackton: Just, like, surrounding the shed.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Did it make it safe?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's DC.
Mike Sackton: Oh, sorry.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: DC16?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It fails at save.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right, so it's grappled. It can't move. It's held by the hand.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: And then I can take a bonus action.
Mike Sackton: Crush it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So the head is gonna squeeze.
David S. Kong: Hell yeah. And then how does this work? Do I have to roll save?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No, no, no, it's automatic. 46 damage. 46? Okay, how much damage?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, that's…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 14 plus 4, 18 damage. 18 damage, okay.
David S. Kong: Yeah, the hand successfully starts crunching on the ship, and you're hearing, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know, actual crunching noises.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So loud that it makes its way into the wanderer's ears.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You're up.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm gonna cast.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Synaptic static.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Also known as… Stank face.
Eric Rosenbaum: Although how far away is the closest of these little ships that?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One of the ships is like, like, the ships are all flying towards you, so yeah, they're getting close.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're within, like…
David S. Kong: 60 feet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So psychic stank energy erupts.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: At a point, In front of one of those ships, it's a 20 foot radius sphere.
Eric Rosenbaum: They have to make an intelligence saving throw.
David S. Kong: Or what?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 8d6 psychic damage on a failed save or half.
Eric Rosenbaum: Unsuccessful, and then also they get the muddled thoughts thing if they fail.
David S. Kong: 16? Does that work or not?
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know… oh no, my Save DC is 15, is that what it's against?
David S. Kong: Yeah. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, Zeno, you made it safe. Does anything happen on, on,
Mike Sackton: It's half damage. Okay.
David S. Kong: How much damage?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oops, I closed the thing, so that's 4D6.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: So I roll that. Let's see.
Eric Rosenbaum: S.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's a total of 20.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, good roll for 46.
David S. Kong: So, but this is like, this is really for whatever is piloting the ship, probably like, it's like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, okay. Yeah, so you definitely, notice and see that, like, the ship that has now interacted with that radius is, like, it's, it's, it's, like, jiggling around. It's not, you know, going on a smooth beeline towards the statue anymore. It's definitely has been…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: been impacted.
David S. Kong: Okay, the first…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The… the third ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: starts to beeline towards.
David S. Kong: They all seem to be avoiding,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, actually, Go ahead.
Tim Sackton: Sorry.
David S. Kong: Give me one second here.
Eric Rosenbaum: So wait, what about our statue action?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You do the statue action last, so little Tony's last.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… You all get the chance to do it after Little Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, so I will, the first, ship, another ship is gonna go, and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They seem to be pretty focused on Shai and Akshaya, and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They attack. Oh, and they hit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Cheyenne Aksha take a, an energy beam strike.
David S. Kong: Which does a bunch of damage.
Eric Rosenbaum: -Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: And now, Huska, it's your turn.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… There's nothing I can really do?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, I will…
Tim Sackton: I mean, we're all inside the statue, right?
David S. Kong: You're inside the statue, you're inside the statue, but.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One thing, Heska, that you can do instead of attacking is you can try to discover.
David S. Kong: An action within the wine.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wait, I have a question.
Eric Rosenbaum: The little statues that attacked us inside the statue.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah. Were they doing eye lasers?
David S. Kong: We're using eye lasers.
Mike Sackton: We gotta, we gotta get the eyes laser.
David S. Kong: Like, big.
Eric Rosenbaum: lasers I'm so glad.
Tim Sackton: Try and activate the eye laser.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Roll a d20.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Any… any plus?
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: is.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The laser's coming out the eyes. It's gonna be a nasty surprise.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You got this, Heska.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You betcha.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm hyping you up. You got one before.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So that's,
Tim Sackton: That's a 16 before any pluses.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you get your acrobatics plus.
Tim Sackton: Okay, so that's a 29.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's all right.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You, all collectively feel,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Behind the statue's eyes, a massive surge of energy building.
David S. Kong: You have, Heska successfully activated the statue's laser eyes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… Up next… The… Dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, the Dreadnought has two attacks, and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Part of how this is all gonna work as well is the Wanderer, Has.
David S. Kong: Hit points, but distributed to different parts of its body.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, boy.
David S. Kong: and.
Eric Rosenbaum: But…
David S. Kong: Dreadnought rolls two attacks.
David S. Kong: 19 hits, and… Four misses. So the dreadnought shoots a massive beam of energy.
David S. Kong: From…
David S. Kong: of one of its… just a massive… I mean, you've never seen anything like this, you don't know what this technology is, but it's, you know, it's like a huge fucking laser beam, gets shot out of the side of the dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And it strikes the, upper chest of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: doing… I'll just tell you these numbers, but it does 128 damage to the shoulder of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, like, a massive chunk of Shoulder, just… obliterates, and I.
Tim Sackton: I will say to little Tony, just as an aside, it's got to be magic, right? Can't you do something about that?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, yeah!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Up next is… Another one of the ships. It is still focused on Aksha.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: It misses.
Mike Sackton: Remember, one of the ships is grappled.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's the… I got it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little Tony, you are up, and after you are up, the Wanderer gets to do its group action.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Awesome, so… Little Tony takes A deep breath.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: uses his Esteem Starry Form ability, which in this context, a starry glowing constellation of a wise old hermit crab wearing a crown appears on his chest.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Giving him advantage on all, concentration checks.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hell yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Restaurant.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's a bonus action, and then… I am going to…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Try Dispel Magic on the Laser Beam.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: part of the Dreadnought, specifically.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And for little Tony, the way Dispel Magic works is,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Everything in the world talks to him, but magic things don't talk to him, and he's deeply offended by this because magical things, like, think they're too good for him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And so…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: He…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Rather than Dispel Magic, this is reskinned as a spell called Fuck Me, No Fuck You!
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He's going to use that.
David S. Kong: Good Friday.
Eric Rosenbaum: 10.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, the magic powering the laser beam to just right off.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: No.
David S. Kong: And what am I… do I roll a save, or what am I doing?
David S. Kong: How does this work?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Look at that.
Tim Sackton: Roll a d20 and add. Schwartz rolls a d20 and adds.
Tim Sackton: Wisdom, we'll just assume 5.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Tim Sackton: Because nobody bothered to do anything about their stats. : And if it's, you have to decide what level of fact the spell is.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Magic.
David S. Kong: Oh, so he has to beat a number that I decide.
Mike Sackton: It's 10 plus the spells level.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's 10 plus the spell's level,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, I got it. All right, go ahead and roll 20.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: With advantage, since you did that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, so my first roll is a 17 before any buffs, and the second roll is a lot less than that.
David S. Kong: Okay, so 17? Is that your… is that your final? Is anybody else helping out here, or is this… we're gonna…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Anyone giving me, like, some extra, some extra hype here?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: I did hype man this round, so I can't do it again, is that correct?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, Bardic inspiration, though.
David S. Kong: Bardag. I forgive you a Bardag. This is nice to have a couple Bards in the group.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll take it. So how do you do that?
Mike Sackton: You added the 10.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, 1d10.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, but tell me, before I roll, like, how are you, how… what is the…
Mike Sackton: the vibe.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is the way that you deliver it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How does, it's, I mean, I do everything.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: With wraps.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hit him!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh man.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's hard to rap over, like, orchestral soundtrack.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little Tony, you're not a phony. Feelin' phony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Macaroni, what's that?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, snap!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You got it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Gonna rock it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I love it, at the top of the lungs.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Lil Tony yells, Fuck me, no, fuck YOU!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And rolls a mighty…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: too.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 2.
Tim Sackton: That doesn't matter because the highest level spells are nine, so you have to beat it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
David S. Kong: So, so as you, and so as you do this too, are you making the, are you thinking about the wanderer actually saying these words out loud?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I am. And like pointing, pointing his finger like right at the, right at the laser beam.
David S. Kong: So, so, you know, a couple things are happening. One, you know, the pulsing behind the laser beams is like, is happening. And then the other thing that's happening is the wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's got an… and it's sort of like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As… As Tony casts his spell magic.
David S. Kong: And this kind of wave of anti-magic shoots out of the fingertip of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, towards the ship?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you get the sense as it kind of, like, rams into the laser beam on the side of the dreadnought that it has succeeded at least partially, if not mostly, or even entirely, of disabling.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One of the lasers on the dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well done.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And now little Tony is the group action. All of you now can, if you so choose, can spend your firstborn action on activating the walker.
Tim Sackton: Let's shoot the laser.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: At least I've been open.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, that engine thing.
Tim Sackton: At the engine thing.
Mike Sackton: No flying in our…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: place here.
Mike Sackton: These guys should not be flying.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Flying with wings.
Mike Sackton: Why do they leave? Totally sacrilegious.
Eric Rosenbaum: plastic.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Nature and Nature's God. Okay.
Mike Sackton: It really is.
David S. Kong: So everybody except Hesta roll a d20.
Mike Sackton: Our skill D20?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Just a straight roller.
David S. Kong: Yeah, no, no, related to your, your, your checklist.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
David S. Kong: What do you guys roll?
Mike Sackton: I got a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 20?
Eric Rosenbaum: 19.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 17.
David S. Kong: 1720?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 19.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How this is working… The three of you,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Not Hesta, all of you are again coordinating all of the functions of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Heska, you are the attack role.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… I…
Eric Rosenbaum: I.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
David S. Kong: And now that you are the attack role as the fucking undefeatable rogue, the Wanderer's probably gonna do pretty well, but.
Tim Sackton: Wow, actually, I'm much worse at attack rolls than skills, but…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Can I take steady aim?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can totally take steady aim with a laser beam, 100% you can.
David S. Kong: You can do rogue shit with the laser beam and a ranged attack weapon.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, that's a…
Tim Sackton: That's, 15…
Eric Rosenbaum: stood.
David S. Kong: 15 attack roll.
Eric Rosenbaum: again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Can anybody help me? Huh?
David S. Kong: Do you have advantage?
Tim Sackton: That was with adventure. Sometimes the dice aren't in your favor.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Damn! Can anybody help him?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes,
Tim Sackton: Anybody hasn't used the reaction with a silvery barbs, maybe?
Mike Sackton: How it's covered, Barb, that doesn't…
Tim Sackton: Oh, that doesn't let me re-roll, it forces them to re-roll.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm going to use a use of Cosmic Omen as a reaction.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hell yeah.
David S. Kong: the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The hermit crab on my chest, like, glows brilliantly, and its little claws go like, clack, clack, clack, clack. And you can add 1d6 to your roll.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, 4.
Tim Sackton: That's a 19.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 19?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… You feel, Heska, in particular.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This, like, throbbing behind your head, like, everybody feels it a little bit, but you really feel it, and you're using.
David S. Kong: Your incredibly now sharp vision as you're staring at this thing and you're like locking in, locking in, locking in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There's no place else to say it, you feel giant fucking laser beams shoot out of your eyeballs, and the giant fucking laser beams shoot out of your eyeballs, and they smash into
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What looks like a shield that is around the ship, so you actually don't hit the ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But you are able to make a devastating attack,
David S. Kong: You do 25d12 damage.
Tim Sackton: Jesus.
Eric Rosenbaum: 25.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: D12, that's funny. Can we do that?
Tim Sackton: I bet we can!
David S. Kong: I mean…
Mike Sackton: You can just click the T12. There we go.
Eric Rosenbaum: That.
Mike Sackton: That's a lot of dice.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Are there…
Tim Sackton: 170.
Mike Sackton: 79.
David S. Kong: 179? All right. You do 179 damage to the shield.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Good job.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Alright, so that is the group action's turn.
David S. Kong: The next enemy ship is Grappled, the set… the last.
Mike Sackton: It can still attack, it just has disadvantage.
David S. Kong: Hold on.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: this… It misses… It can't move.
Mike Sackton: But it can attack, but it has…
David S. Kong: Yeah, it missed. The last enemy ship.
Mike Sackton: Or I could…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Try and escape.
Mike Sackton: The ground.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're not that smart. This one attacks, again,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Akshay and Shai, this one… this one hits again!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They look, I mean, they're fine, but they're, they're definitely a little damaged.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Akshat and, Shai… Go and shoot at the grapple ship.
David S. Kong: Do they get advantage because it's grappled?
Mike Sackton: No.
Tim Sackton: No.
David S. Kong: You know? Fuck.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Now, you only get an advantage if it's restrained.
David S. Kong: Okay, well they hit it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They hit it, and they…
David S. Kong: This one is quite wounded. This looks like this ship is the grappled ship is not in great shape.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sculpin, to you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, so here's a question.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We're not, like, part of the Wanderer, are we? Like…
Mike Sackton: Can I cast Mirror Image to make three Wanderers appear?
David S. Kong: Wow.
Eric Rosenbaum: Funny idea.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wow.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can try.
David S. Kong: You can totally try.
Tim Sackton: Oh, wait, I have an idea.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You get 100% try.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Think about all your spells, guys. You have some pretty fucking interesting spells that…
Tim Sackton: Okay.
David S. Kong: this concept.
Mike Sackton: Yes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But this is great. So wait, so how does it normally work to decide whether or not you succeed? To make a mirror image? No, mirror image normally just works on yourself.
Mike Sackton: And it creates 3 images, and then any attack, you roll…
Mike Sackton: a D6, and if you get 3 or higher, you hit a duplicate. If you hit a duplicate, it gets destroyed.
David S. Kong: Oh, so it's a defensive thing, so…
Mike Sackton: air.
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, totally. Okay, but make a.
David S. Kong: Make an Arcana check to try to succeed to make this happen with the…
Mike Sackton: 29.
David S. Kong: All right.
David S. Kong: So, Sculpa, as you sit in your super comfortable favorite chair, God, you wish you could take this throne home with you.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer, giant fucking statue, still has his arm stretched out. Laser beam shot out of the eyeball, but now he's, you know, with a fingertip pointed out after saying fuck you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then you see shimmering, shimmering, shimmering. And then two giant fucking replica Wanderers appear on either side of the main Wanderer, all pointed at the Chaelite or at the Dreadnought, saying, "Fuck you.
David S. Kong: So you have succeeded. There's now three wanderers on the shore.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Then… With my bonus action, I will crush The ship that is grappled.
David S. Kong: strong.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let's see, hold on… I can…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well, it's grappled, you can take a bonus action to crush it. Another 46 damage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Crappy role, but…
Mike Sackton: 15 damage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's enough. The ship, you have, like, crunched the cockpit, and, like, there's, like, a little bloody pulpy, like, kind of feeling. Like, whatever was inside, you killed it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That…
Mike Sackton: I'll just drop it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Does it fall? It falls. It falls and crashes beneath the seat.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well done. Alright.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: Ahem.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: She…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Not even a bunch.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How close… is the closest…
Eric Rosenbaum: of the ships.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're all close, I mean, basically, like, like, how this, this has unfolded, at least nobody's, like, flown far away, like, they're, like, Akshara and Shai are kind of, like.
David S. Kong: They're trying to figure out how to both attack the dreadnought and also, you know, attack some of the ships. So everything is like within like, you know, 100 feet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Thinking about… Wall of force, but that's not that useful.
Mike Sackton: Can you make a wall of force to, like, cut the ship? I forget, does the wall of force go through things?
Tim Sackton: You can't cut things in half if you try and go through things.
Tim Sackton: They end up on one side or the other.
Eric Rosenbaum: It gets pushed, yeah.
Mike Sackton: But could… and I can't float in the middle of the air, can I?
Eric Rosenbaum: again.
Mike Sackton: Well, can you just put a wall of force in front of the laser beam?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, because it can't shoot us, but we couldn't shoot it. Oh, but it's, I could block it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Mike. Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Mike.
David S. Kong: Stop it.
Tim Sackton: I have an idea that… So, go ahead, but don't worry about blocking us.
Tim Sackton: If my idea works.
Mike Sackton: Just make a little domed wall of force around the gun port on the Dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It won't move with the dreadnought.
Mike Sackton: That's true.
Tim Sackton: No.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
Tim Sackton: I cannot can just move out of the way.
Mike Sackton: That's true, oh, that's true. That it doesn't attach, does it?
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm not sure.
Tim Sackton: It's stationary.
David S. Kong: Sculpin successfully casted mirror image, so now there's two mirror images of the giant thing, all pointed at the dreadnought saying, fuck you.
David S. Kong: Why don't we… Brilliant. Love it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you Guys, should I make like a…
Eric Rosenbaum: A wall of sound shield in front of the chest of the wanderer so that we can't get hit by anything.
Tim Sackton: Oh, that's a good idea.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So I… An incredibly loud sound spins up.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Starting from Zeno's chest as a deep humming.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then this reverberation turns into a shimmering, of.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 10 10 by 10 foot panels.
Eric Rosenbaum: Floating in front of the chest where we're sitting.
Eric Rosenbaum: So… What's a rectangle made out of 10 panels? Like, 2x5, I guess?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 20 high by 50 across.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's like a little.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I mean, that's proper chest protection in case you take a direct hit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: So nothing can physically pass through the wall. It is immune to all damage and can't be dispelled by dispel magic. The disintegrate spell destroys the wall instantly.
Eric Rosenbaum: The wall also extends into the ethereal plane and blocks ethereal travel.
Tim Sackton: It doesn't move, so if we move, or if the ship moves around us…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It says…
Eric Rosenbaum: It can be vertical, it can be free-floating, or resting on a solid surface, so could it be resting on the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Chest.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You could position it that way. Yeah, you could, you can find a way to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Kind of crush it into the stone.
Eric Rosenbaum: Funny how a giant statue is both a solid surface and a moving object.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright. No, but you can, like, you can, like, crunch it in, and have it kind of, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
David S. Kong: You can do that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Now there's just this deep roaring sound emitting from the chest of the…
David S. Kong: Hell yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: The Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Nice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, up next is another one of the enemy fighters, and the fighter ships all seem to be going after Shai, and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And Aksha… This is Haska to you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, I would like to cast Enlarge on the statue.
David S. Kong: Oh my God. Oh my God. Tim.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a ridiculous idea.
Tim Sackton: though.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
Tim Sackton: Jessica is gonna lean down.
David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: put his hand.
Tim Sackton: On the floor of the room that we're in, and it's gonna be like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just thinking we're not big enough, you know?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: thought a 100 foot statue was cool. Wait till you see this.
Tim Sackton: And I will double the size of the statue, in all.
David S. Kong: Oh my god. Holy fuck. Do you have to roll anything or does that just automatically work?
Tim Sackton: No, just unless… unless the statue doesn't want to be
Tim Sackton: Enlarged, in which case it has to make a constitution save.
David S. Kong: Hey, man. I mean, you're fucking you know, you're divine firstborn. Go ahead and fucking works. Yeah. I mean, there's no roles. Yeah. That you the this okay. Well, the one thing here is, do the mirror images also gain change size?
Mike Sackton: Yeah, I think so.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, because they're con. They're. They're.
Tim Sackton: They're just constantly moving around, so nobody can tell which one the correct status is.
David S. Kong: Oh my god, are you fucking serious? So all three statues double in size?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah. Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, so just, like, as you, as this is all unfolding, right? Because obviously, you know, the, the, like, the dragonettes are kind of like, oh, like, you know, what the is going on? But now, like, seeing all the stats, it's like, any ones that are not, that are not hidden are like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Holy shit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, that works.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, the mirrors are, like, mimicking literally everything the Wanderer does, and, like, are constantly shifting position. The whole idea is you can't tell which one you're supposed to hit.
David S. Kong: So the Dreadnought now has two attacks, and I think
David S. Kong: Is, I mean, it's, it's obviously, you know, it's, it's a fucking, you know, huge ass ship, so it doesn't emote, but
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as you study the Dreadnought closely, there's five, it looks like, big guns, or like weapons on the ship itself. You've disabled one.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One of them… points.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you see it, How it's being directed, and it looks like it's aiming towards the village.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And it shoots an energy beam.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Towards the village, which is at…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The far right base near the edge of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 18.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You all see, and this is, I mean, I don't know how you all experience this emotionally, but you see a massive energy beam coming from this ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: obliterating the town square of the Wanderer's Village, and all of the nearby homes are eviscerated, and this is something just…
David S. Kong: A type of violence that.
David S. Kong: I don't know if any of you have ever seen or experienced before. I mean, you hunt, you know, that's the closest thing. It's like this natural…
David S. Kong: Thing, you see violence in that way, but not like this.
David S. Kong: And you hear… Or you can imagine as you see dragonettes that have not fully fled.
David S. Kong: In terror.
David S. Kong: Flying away from the village.
David S. Kong: And there's scrambling, and there's chaos.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: In the village.
David S. Kong: That's the first attack.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The second tact.
David S. Kong: He's going for the Wanderer's Pad.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Really.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: misses.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Another enemy ship.
David S. Kong: veers and flies towards the Wanderer's head.
David S. Kong: Miss us!
David S. Kong: Well, Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Is there, like, a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Is there a bridge? Is there a, like, a place where there are people controlling this thing? Like, is that obvious or visible in any way?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can try to locate that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, I'll do that. Here's what I'm thinking, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I've got Wall of Stone, and if I can just wrap that around, like, all of their windows, and effectively blind them…
Eric Rosenbaum: 12.30.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Nice. Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, but, but are you, so if you want, you can spend your entire action on trying to.
David S. Kong: Find consciousness on the ship, is that what you're trying to do?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: But like, what are you trying to, how are you trying to figure out the location of the, of the bridge or the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Just like… yeah, what a good question.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna ask the ship, I'm gonna ask the ship, where, where are the people on you?
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
Mike Sackton: Ha ha ha!
David S. Kong: Make a persuasion check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, that's a 15?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): But wait a second, I am going to… use,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): my helpful friend skill to give myself advantage, and Glenda the seagull is gonna, after she hears me starting to talk, be like, no, no, no, no, that is not the way to approach this conversation whatsoever. Try this instead. Okay. So I'm gonna re-roll that persuasion.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And that is a 23.
David S. Kong: Okay, so what are you saying to the ship? How are you, what's the conversation right now? What are you trying to say to the ship?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So, like, my initial attempt was to be just really friendly with it, and be like, hey, buddy, like, it's so good to meet you, I know we haven't met yet, but when Glenda's like, no, no, no, no, like, this is a very mean ship, it only responds to, like, forcefulness, and so my second attempt was like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You fucking chip, where are the people on y'all? Fuck you up if you don't tell me where the people are on you.
David S. Kong: So the ship, so funny that you're talking to the ship now. The ship, It's…
David S. Kong: The ship is definitely not nice. The ship definitely has, like, a vibe of, like, I'm here to fuck shit up and destroy things and I am
David S. Kong: It's kind of like a chain pitbull.
David S. Kong: It's like what this shit feels like, you know?
David S. Kong: It potentially could be used for other things, but it's been trained to bite and tear and destroy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… but you do get a sense from the ship that, yeah, there's a place that, if you got to it, would hurt me a lot.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you basically, you know, if you kind of look, you know, imagining the, the, the size of the ship.
David S. Kong: It's essentially like the center of like behind where this big energy beam is. There's sort of like this is the iris of the ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And there's something behind that, that…
David S. Kong: if you destroyed it would probably be a pretty good thing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, fabulous, I'll relay that, like, that's where we should be focusing our I blast, sir.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Any attacks on the ship itself?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Cool. I think that's my action. I think the persuasion is that action.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What are y'all making the Wanderer do?
Tim Sackton: So it's giant now, so I think we should just punch that spot.
Eric Rosenbaum: definitely.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Just like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right.
Tim Sackton: But, just like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
David S. Kong: Let's fucking go.
David S. Kong: Oh, man, this is… this is really good. Okay, okay, okay.
David S. Kong: Okay, wait, so how does the, because you're enlarged, how does that impact damage?
Tim Sackton: Well, it's up to you. Technically, according to the rules, it adds 1D4.
David S. Kong: No, no, no, no.
Tim Sackton: I would probably let it do a little more than that.
David S. Kong: No, no, yeah, no, I will, I will, I will, I will.
Eric Rosenbaum: MD 400.
David S. Kong: It only does 1d4. What a shitty spell, man.
Tim Sackton: No, no, it's supposed to be like you, you go from medium to large.
David S. Kong: Okay, but not, not, you know, god statue to, like, double god statue? Yeah, exactly. Alright, alright, alright, that's fine, that's fine. Alright, so go ahead and, so everybody not has to roll.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Your check.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What are your roles?
Mike Sackton: 18.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Team for me.
Tim Sackton: Oh, Zeno got a 26. That's sick.
Eric Rosenbaum: 26.
David S. Kong: Nice. Alright, so that's 2.
David S. Kong: And Heska, you are the attack roll. I know, so you're doing a punch, right?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Alright, Husko, what you got?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Still steady aim.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, that's better, a 26.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 26 hits, and 2 out of 3 of you,
David S. Kong: We're successful in your check. And you're doubled in size, right?
Tim Sackton: Yep.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, so the Wanderer, like, wheels back, and just, you know, boxers punch.
Tim Sackton: And we're aiming for whatever… No, yeah, but the virus.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, right to the iris of the ship. Like, it's not the perfect punch, but it's still a devastating punch.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you do 25d12 plus 100 damage.
David S. Kong: 25D12.
Tim Sackton: Whoops. I did 20, 60, 12. I don't know. Oh, there.
David S. Kong: That's fine, that's fine.
Tim Sackton: Tommy.
David S. Kong: How much damage?
Tim Sackton: 283.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
David S. Kong: 283, alright. So, with that punch.
David S. Kong: You see this shield, the shield's not, it's invisible, but like, as you're punching and hitting it, that's when it, like, the shield just.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Disintegrates.
David S. Kong: And you have successfully breached the shield of the dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Now, up next is… Enemy 1, who continues to attack…
David S. Kong: Oh, they hit… okay, so Akshar and Shai, by the way, are, like, they're, like, bloody. They're, like, not looking good. They're, they're, they're in serious danger.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They are still at the fight, though, and they continue to try to attack.
David S. Kong: The one wounded…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Enemy ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… They hit. That one is now bloodied.
David S. Kong: With the laser, Sculpted is to you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So… The… the, our buddies are doing poorly, is that what you were just saying?
David S. Kong: They are. Yeah, they're bloody.
Mike Sackton: Alright.
David S. Kong: They're.
Mike Sackton: anybody.
David S. Kong: But you also, like, through the telepathic connection, they're like, don't worry about us, we're fine.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
David S. Kong: Bring down the dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm gonna shoot a lightning bolt at the… I'm gonna cast a 5th level lightning bolt at the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: At the… there's a weak spot now, right?
David S. Kong: Yeah, oh yeah. Well, the shield's gone, so you can attack wherever you want.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well, then I'll try and hit one of the,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'll try and hit one of the, guns.
David S. Kong: Now, so here's kind of an interesting thing, and this happened a little bit with Little Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: When he cast, because when he cast the spell Magic, it actually came out of the fingertip of the Wanderer, which was
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, a strange little thing. So,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can… go ahead and cast Lightning Bolt.
David S. Kong: When you cast Lightning Bolt, like, as a human, like, what happens normally? Like, where does the lightning come from? Does it come from the sky, or does it come from the…
Mike Sackton: No, no, it comes from you. It's a line. It comes from you, it's a line.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Actually… Great.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, it's a hundred foot…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I mean, I'm gonna try and line it up so it hits some of the little things as well as… but I don't know if there's any little things in front of us.
David S. Kong: There's one, there's one you can hit, there's one that's bloody.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So it makes a deck saving throw.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Massive damage roll. 31 damage.
David S. Kong: That's enough. You disable that one. That one.
Mike Sackton: And then it keeps going and hits the dreadnought as well.
David S. Kong: Okay, cool. And how much damage does it do the dreaded.
Mike Sackton: Day 31.
David S. Kong: Okay, but this one's a direct hit to the eye.
David S. Kong: 30 damage, you said?
Mike Sackton: 31.
David S. Kong: Okay, great.
Mike Sackton: And then I'm gonna move the giant fist.
Mike Sackton: And just punch right where the lightning bolt hit.
David S. Kong: Wait, how are you doing that? Oh, oh, with your, your fit. Okay. Yeah, yeah. Good.
Mike Sackton: The giant hand is still there. It's a bonus action to move.
David S. Kong: Yep, I got it, I got it, great.
Mike Sackton: 5th level spells are awesome!
David S. Kong: I love it!
David S. Kong: Do I have to roll a save?
Mike Sackton: No, no, I rolled the hit because I'm punching it this time instead of grappling. Nice. So it's, it's,
Mike Sackton: Plus a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, D20…
Mike Sackton: Crappy world, though. 9. Oh, no, 13. But it's still…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So I did this.
David S. Kong: All the damage adds up, so the 13 right to the iris of the ship.
Mike Sackton: 13th ahead.
Tim Sackton: I think they had.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, you missed? Oh, okay. Yeah. That bad.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm just trying to figure out what I can do, because…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The Wall of…
Eric Rosenbaum: Sound is a concentration spell.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, I was thinking about using my, sick burn.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But the problem is… how can I do that? Because I'm, like, inside the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Can I… can we make the statue, like…
Eric Rosenbaum: E.
Tim Sackton: You gotta. You gotta get the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Get the statue…
Tim Sackton: To do a call and response with the dreadnought.
Eric Rosenbaum: I was thinking about that too, but what would that be exactly?
David S. Kong: I mean, you've already pointed at it and told it, fuck you. Like, there's a mirror, there's, like, mirrors, mirrors, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: true.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That are… that are… You know, that's already happened.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Call and response with a hand gesture.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You could be like,
David S. Kong: And then… and then the Dreadnought, I don't know, we'll see.
Tim Sackton: And then the two mirror images do it too, so you.
David S. Kong: You can get a whole little synchronized dance room. You literally have like a little mini dance crew. Oh my god. Okay, yeah. Do it, do it, do it. Yeah, this is this is too.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, I'm gonna, like, just, like… Went down at the ground.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hoping it will like nosedive.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: When I point down, You…
Eric Rosenbaum: Dive to the ground when I point down, you dive to the ground so we're just like.
David S. Kong: Oh my god, okay, alright, okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: having.
David S. Kong: And how does this work? Do I roll a save, or what's the deal?
Eric Rosenbaum: Let me check mine… It is.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it's the same. It should be like DC 16 or something like that.
David S. Kong: Nice.
Eric Rosenbaum: Availability is…
David S. Kong: Oh my god, okay.
Tim Sackton: 50th.
David S. Kong: I don't even know what this means, but the Dreadnought fails its save. So what happens now?
Eric Rosenbaum: It has to respond in some way to my call.
Tim Sackton: It has to use its action to…
David S. Kong: What? Like what about that?
Eric Rosenbaum: yet.
David S. Kong: One of its actions.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, one of its actions.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: To like, somehow gesture with the whole ship.
David S. Kong: Okay, all right, all right, all right.
Eric Rosenbaum: Three statues.
David S. Kong: So, okay. So, does it happen now or is it later when.
Tim Sackton: No, on his turn.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay.
David S. Kong: And… Alright, so is that your turn?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, Heska, before your turn, the Dreadnought is using a legendary action.
David S. Kong: And is now firing up the main cannon that it has.
David S. Kong: That actually is a little wounded because it's behind the iris but is now firing up the main cannon.
David S. Kong: And is shooting it at the Wanderer's upper body.
David S. Kong: And… Wait, what happens to the force field, Eric? What's the deal with that shield?
Eric Rosenbaum: Nothing can pass through.
Tim Sackton: Protecting our chest, nothing can pass through it.
David S. Kong: But, so if it, if you get a direct strike to the chest, what happens?
Tim Sackton: nothing.
David S. Kong: Nothing?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: It'll just stop.
Mike Sackton: Also, if it's shooting at us, it still has to get to the mirror image if it hits.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's right.
David S. Kong: Oh, jeez.
Mike Sackton: So if you hit, tell me, and I'll roll to see if it hit the image instead of us.
David S. Kong: All right. 50. Yeah, that hits. So it does hit. It hits. It hits the upper body.
Mike Sackton: So, let's see here…
David S. Kong: Tell me if it hits the mirror.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, it hit an image.
David S. Kong: No, okay. So you like the dreadnought like had been charging its energy beam unleashes a huge one and it passes harmlessly.
Mike Sackton: And the image disappears. I mean, it's gone now.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay.
Mike Sackton: There's only two left, there's two images left.
David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: All right, the dreadnought goes back to charging its beam and we go to Esta.
Tim Sackton: I want to try and figure out if the statue has any…
Tim Sackton: Like shields, now that I've seen the dreadnought with a shield, I'm like, do we have a shield?
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice. All right. That's a great question.
David S. Kong: Very good question. Okay.
Tim Sackton: I'll use my action to investigate.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, cool.
David S. Kong: What do you roll?
Tim Sackton: That's a 29.
David S. Kong: Dude, what the fuck, man? All right. So what describe what are you? What are you? What are you like? How are you investigating if there's a.
Tim Sackton: So I'm… so I'm just… so I'm thinking about… about Heska's…
Tim Sackton: Sorry, about Zeno's spell, I'm trying to, like, tune into the
Tim Sackton: The sound and I'm like, convincing the, I'm getting the, like, trying to get the.
Tim Sackton: The.
Tim Sackton: statue to listen, and be like, like, you can do that over your whole body, right? Just make it bigger.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, nice, nice.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: As you're tuning into that, it's like a tuning fork, you're kind of exploring these different frequencies.
David S. Kong: And sure enough, you're kind of tuning into the force field, and tuning into the force field, and then you start to feel as though, indeed, you could also tune into that exact same frequency, and that it might be possible to create a similar-sized shield anywhere on the body.
David S. Kong: So force field unlocked but you can only, you have to position it, it doesn't cover the entire body, you have to position, you have to position over a body part.
David S. Kong: Heska, is that your, your move?
Tim Sackton: yeah, yeah.
Tim Sackton: Otherwise…
Tim Sackton: I… yeah, there's nothing else I can really do.
David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: Well, think a little bit about what you all want to do with your attack, too, if you're still satisfied with punching and lasers, or, if there's anything else you want to do. I mean…
Mike Sackton: The Waze has been doing pretty good for us at the punching.
David S. Kong: Punching was good, but there might be.
Mike Sackton: I mean, could we, like, grab the ship and just, like, throw it into the water?
David S. Kong: You 100% could.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think that's good.
David S. Kong: You can do whatever you want, guys. You can do whatever the fuck you want right now. Like, this is a kind of a moment. You are literally, four of you are like cockpit cockpitting a fucking giant ancient divine statue Mecca. So this is the time to be creative if you want to do something fun.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Eric Rosenbaum: Grab a little ship, throw it into the big one.
David S. Kong: That's true.
Eric Rosenbaum: together.
David S. Kong: The Dreadnought, so the Dreadnought, one of its attacks has been, is now, what happened again? He, he's, he's, he's, he lost one attack. Oh, because the, that laser, like, when you said, when I got that, and that laser went, and, like, literally the energy beam goes, like, it just cuts through the water, and there's, like, a
David S. Kong: sizzle of steam as this like energy beam cuts through the water and you get the sense too that like whoever's like piloting the the sizzling beam is like like you know literally like trying to trying to like you know get back at you but but has has unfortunately failed.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: If you For its other attack.
David S. Kong: This one is targeting the Dragonette village yet again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Ugh.
Eric Rosenbaum: I should have put up the wall of force down there. Oh well.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: big enough, I guess.
Mike Sackton: I can actually, I should have used Big Beast to try and defend it too.
David S. Kong: This one, it's, it's a partial hit, it's, it like misses the heart of the village, but still like, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Rips through, like, a bunch of the homes, like, on the edge of the outskirts of the village.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Up next is,
David S. Kong: I'm next is old Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I can't do anything with the statue on my own, right? Like, we have to do it all together.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Correct.
David S. Kong: First born action is all together. You can do your own personal action with something you might want to do, but.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I could use it to figure out another…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Feature of the statue…
David S. Kong: explore.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): what you do.
David S. Kong: Also, too, remember, as a spellcaster, you can also, like, kind of cast spells through the Wanderer, like, it's like, you also, like, you know, it's like when, when, Sculpet shot lightning bolts, it, like, came out of the fingertip of the Wanderer, you know, it's like, you can kind of mediate, the Wanderer's a bit your medium as well, if you want to cast spells, but also, unlocking shit is pretty fucking great, because after you unlock it, you can use it immediately now, little Tony, so.
David S. Kong: If there's something you want to, you know, you're able to make a force field, you're able to shoot laser beams out of your eyes, like, what are you trying to do with that?
Mike Sackton: I mean… There's something to be said for just how many quasars does it have?
David S. Kong: How many ladies?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: just does that.
Mike Sackton: I've tried that.
David S. Kong: The Dreadnought had 5, 1 is disabled, there's 4 more, there's 4 more lasers and like the main, the main, you know.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Iris, would you.
Tim Sackton: I mean, you could just try and disable another laser.
Mike Sackton: I was gonna say.
Tim Sackton: It's not bad.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'll do another Dispel Magic on another laser. Nice, okay, yeah, not just that. I mean, do I have to roll a save?
Mike Sackton: No, no, no, Schwartz has to roll.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Better than that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's not.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: idea.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I don't think I can even, like.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Get there.
David S. Kong: Don't rescue that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Our little friends.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Good effort. Everybody, what are you doing with the Wanderer?
Tim Sackton: I think we should just punch the cockpit. Those shields are down, right?
David S. Kong: The shoulders down? You have these.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think we should do like a, like a.
David S. Kong: Did almost 400.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Action movie like Jumping Punch, like where we jump up in the air and then…
Tim Sackton: Like, slam it from. Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or I'm trying to like punch him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Punch all the way through it to the other side, is the…
Eric Rosenbaum: Bear bear hug it into the wall of sound.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like, crush it against the impenetrable surface.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We could like tackle it into the water too against the wall of sound.
Eric Rosenbaum: I like that.
David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're just like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Swat it down into the water like a huge.
David S. Kong: Decisions, decisions.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What are y'all doing?
Tim Sackton: Punch did a ton of damage, let's just hit punch the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: cockpit.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Punch the cockpit. Okay.
David S. Kong: Are you gonna, are you gonna do, a theatrical, like, you know, jump up in the air and, like, you know, like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's like a spin kick.
Mike Sackton: No, I'm envisioning more, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: The Roundhouse.
Mike Sackton: smash through and like grab anything inside the cockpit, pull it out, like throw it into the.
David S. Kong: Wow.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Looks.
Tim Sackton: I know, okay, okay, okay. Can we use… So, my…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: My…
Tim Sackton: Talent is the hunter's pounce.
David S. Kong: Oh my god.
Tim Sackton: If we use Hunter's Pounce.
David S. Kong: Let's go.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 2.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Tube.
Tim Sackton: Hunters pounce the pilot out of the ship because I'm supposed to be able to like grab and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can. You can.
David S. Kong: You totally can!
David S. Kong: So you're gonna punch through the iris and then reach out and try to grab whomever or whatever is piloting the ship and then pull it out?
Tim Sackton: Yes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, let's fucking do it.
David S. Kong: What, what, and what, is it an ability check or whatever, to see if you succeed in that?
Tim Sackton: It's an attack roll, but if I…
Tim Sackton: If I want to try and grab something, I also have to make an acrobatics check against whatever DC.
David S. Kong: Okay, excellent. So first, everybody not HESCA roll your checks.
Eric Rosenbaum: I still have advantage, right?
Mike Sackton: I don't know if Schwartz casts something that requires concentration.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh…
Mike Sackton: But I don't think he did.
Tim Sackton: anything.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Not yet.
Tim Sackton: So you still have advantage.
Mike Sackton: Schwartz, you don't, because I'm concentrating on Digby's hands.
Eric Rosenbaum: Jesus.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: and 26.
Mike Sackton: I got a 22.
Eric Rosenbaum: I got a 14.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I can give you another D6.
David S. Kong: See that?
Mike Sackton: 21, sorry, I got a 21.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'll take the D6.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's another 3.
Tim Sackton: 17.
David S. Kong: 17, okay.
David S. Kong: And then, what did you roll, Tony?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 26.
David S. Kong: A 26? Okay, alright, alright, that's good. That's- this is- this is strong.
David S. Kong: All right, what happens to you, Heska?
Tim Sackton: Oh, no!
Tim Sackton: I rolled an 11 to hit.
Eric Rosenbaum: -Oh.
David S. Kong: Oh, man.
Tim Sackton: I rolled a two and a one.
David S. Kong: So.
Mike Sackton: Can you… can we give you a verdict?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah. Oh, right.
David S. Kong: 11's not… I mean, yeah, see, yeah, why not?
Mike Sackton: Plus 1D10!
David S. Kong: I mean, yeah, sure, sure, it helps, that'll help.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Verdict.
Tim Sackton: Oh, there we go.
Tim Sackton: An 18.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, alright.
David S. Kong: So, so, your, your, your full plan does not go as succeeded, but you still make a glance.
Tim Sackton: It shouldn't have been so tricky.
David S. Kong: You still made a glancing hit, and you still, like, do make contact and have a strong hit. You do 10d12 plus 25. You would have done a lot more damage if you'd done it the other way, but 10d12 is kind of on the low end of the damage that the statue does, so…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's.
Tim Sackton: But do I still get to try and grab something, right?
David S. Kong: You can still try to grab something, yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, so that's a…
Tim Sackton: 87 damage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 87. Okay.
Tim Sackton: And that's a 29 for my acrobatics check to grab whatever's in the cockpit.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: So.
David S. Kong: Are you, like, squeezing it and grabbing it? Like, are you, like.
Tim Sackton: No, no, I want to rip it out. Like, the whole idea is the… it's a pounce, right? So I'm, like, diving on… it's like to catch fish, right? So I'm trying to… I'm trying to catch the fish that's lingering in.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, so…
Eric Rosenbaum: It may be damaged in the process, whatever is.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it's okay if it's damaged in the process.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I think it's, it's gonna be bloodied and destroyed by the giant hand that's tearing through the fucking hull and, yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, you know, I mean, it's epic. You punch through the center. I mean, not as crazily epic as it could be, but still, because of Heska's skill, you're able to reach, pull out.
David S. Kong: And unfortunately, Heska, whatever was in your hand is just like, you feel it go.
Tim Sackton: I'm not used to this. I'm not used.
David S. Kong: You do not have the dexterity to, like, not.
David S. Kong: Prevent, you know, just squishing whatever's inside.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But.
David S. Kong: After doing that, the ship now is like, just suddenly is like, not, it's not, it just looks like it is not doing well, it's, it's kind of just in a weird, it looks like it's lost its bearings.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, enemy ship… guys, this is very bad.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Shai and Akshay have taken a blow and they are going down.
David S. Kong: Oh. You see their ship. You see them, you see them, you hear them as they're going down. We'll be fine, we'll be fine, we'll be fine. And then suddenly.
David S. Kong: No more, no more sound out of them as they crash.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So there's still one more ship left.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Yeah, there's only one more ship left, and now we go back to Sculpin.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I am going to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Grab the ship that's left?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A.
Mike Sackton: And then… wait.
Mike Sackton: Let's see, I'm gonna…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I guess I'll try and…
Mike Sackton: Cast another…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Lightning Bolt, I don't have that much else…
Mike Sackton: Oh, wait, wait a minute…
David S. Kong: Lightning bolt's good.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Can I?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Can I,
Mike Sackton: I know, that takes concentration, never mind. Yeah, I'm gonna cast the lightning bolt.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm gonna grab… I'm gonna… I'm gonna take the little ship and grab it with Bigby's again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then I'm gonna fire a lightning bolt through the Wonder Sand at the, like, into the cockpit area of the Dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of the Dreadnought? Okay. Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right, so let's do the enemy first. What happens? The little chef has to make a deck saving throw. DC 816. Fails.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, it is grappled.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And it takes…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 12, 12 damage.
David S. Kong: Called it. Or, Zeno.
Mike Sackton: And then I'm gonna shoot a lightning bolt.
David S. Kong: At the, at the, at the,
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Terrible damage roll. 28. That's not awful, actually.
Mike Sackton: Save for half, so it's definitely worth it.
David S. Kong: The eye is bloodied. I mean, it's definitely you are you are the dreadnought is is on its last legs for sure.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, if I'm gonna maintain the wall of sound… I can't cast another spell…
Eric Rosenbaum: I can just do another call and response.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, because you can keep going for every second it has to make another save.
David S. Kong: There's only three more lasers.
Eric Rosenbaum: So, and we still have the illusory statues as well?
David S. Kong: One more, there's one more mirror statue left, yep.
Mike Sackton: There should be 2 more, there was 3 originally.
Tim Sackton: It starts with 3.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Two more left.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So we're gonna do, like, a Temptation style, like… Triple spin. Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then point.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, the, like…
David S. Kong: Oh, I love it.
Eric Rosenbaum: And so it has to do the same.
David S. Kong: And they're double size, they're enlarged, so they're twice.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, of course, of course, okay.
David S. Kong: Does it work? Do I do I save or or will I save or Yeah. Sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wisdom save DC 15, right?
David S. Kong: 14, I fell. All right, you succeed. You do your point, and now the commander of the third laser is compelled to respond.
David S. Kong: All right.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Asuka.
Tim Sackton: So we've got the shield, we've got…
Mike Sackton: Wait, has somebody activated the shield? I forget, did we…
David S. Kong: No, you used your.
Tim Sackton: No, because I think it's. I mean, it's not that useful to us while the mirror images are.
Mike Sackton: That's true. Yeah, no, that's true.
Tim Sackton: But I've got, I can't cast another concentration spell because.
Mike Sackton: God, I'm large going.
Tim Sackton: I've got Enlarge going, and…
Eric Rosenbaum: just.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I can't really do… yeah, there's not much I can do. I mean, the one thing I'll try and do…
Eric Rosenbaum: See if we can fly.
Tim Sackton: I was gonna see if we could jump.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: But maybe we could fly.
Mike Sackton: On to the ship.
Tim Sackton: I'm just gonna see, like, like, I'm gonna test out the legs, you know?
Tim Sackton: What's this thing's… what's this thing's, like, acrobatic potential?
David S. Kong: Oh, I love it. Okay, great. Do this with advantage. Make your check with advantage.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Tim Sackton: So that's a 27.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you get the sense, Heska, that this thing can fucking jump.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
Tim Sackton: Okay, so we are bigger than the Dreadnought now, right?
David S. Kong: You are bigger than us, Brenda.
Tim Sackton: We're doing next time. Just jump right on top of it, like jump up, land on it, we'll crush it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Love it, love it, love it.
Mike Sackton: Okay?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: do that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, now… Oh, actually, the description…
Mike Sackton: No, it goes, right?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes. So the Dreadnought is fucking, it's not, if it could be pissed, it is. It's going to use, it's going to, it still has one of his attacks, do I still get, do I get both my attacks back now?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: No, no, because you're still calling the spots. You failed the save again.
Tim Sackton: adjust.
David S. Kong: Yeah, so that laser… okay, so that laser,
Eric Rosenbaum: All right.
David S. Kong: Zeno is like, "Oh yeah?" And they try to spin, and then the laser beam goes and like spins, and again, you know, just fires this like random round, like the potion sizzling through the water again.
David S. Kong: One, it uses as another legendary action, its main gun, which now it is charging and shooting.
David S. Kong: At the wanderer's upper body.
David S. Kong: Okay, this definitely hits.
Mike Sackton: Nope, it hits the mirror image.
David S. Kong: Oh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): have.
Eric Rosenbaum: guys.
Mike Sackton: Another one goes away. I have one left.
Tim Sackton: One mirror lamp.
David S. Kong: Fucking drunk.
Tim Sackton: So we've got one. We've got one shot at jumping on it. Then I think we need that. We should activate the shields.
Mike Sackton: Okay. The giant laser…
David S. Kong: Wait, wait, wait, the Dreadnought still has one more attack. The Dreadnought still has one more regular laser attack. Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It is going to shoot at the village one more time.
David S. Kong: It misses, well, it, it, it again, it's just bad aim, everybody inside, whatever the fuck is piloting the ship is like, the call and response thing is throwing everybody up, there's like, dance battles inside the turrets and everybody's like, trying to, you know, do this and that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they…
David S. Kong: They, you know, again, they sizzle some of the villages on the outside, the buildings, but they don't do a direct hit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: All right, little Tony.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I am going to cast Wall of Stone.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But I'm gonna stack all of my segments of the wall together into a thing that the,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That the statue can hold so that when we jump up on it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, wow.
David S. Kong: gonna.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Dab through the whole dreadnought using this giant.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, Stone Mall.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Spike thing.
David S. Kong: So you fabricate that?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So I fabricate that in the hands of the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, you, you successfully fabricated it is now the, the massive doubly enlarged.
David S. Kong: Divine Stone statue now has a giant mall in its hand, which appears in both of the other also mirror-imaged giant statues.
David S. Kong: Are you all now, what are you all doing for your, for your firstborn action?
Tim Sackton: I think.
Mike Sackton: right?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Jump.
Tim Sackton: And just try and land on it and like knock it out of the sky.
David S. Kong: All right. And then smash the thing right there. All right. Let's fucking go. Everybody but Heska, do your checks.
Mike Sackton: 28?
David S. Kong: Okay?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 22.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 20.
David S. Kong: All right, this is the first time you have all okay, so all three of you successfully hit so this is you haven't had a perfect sync attack yet, but you this may be it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, that's.
David S. Kong: can successfully,
Eric Rosenbaum: Awesome.
Tim Sackton: So I'm going to argue if we're trying to jump on top of the ship, this should be acrobatics, not an attack roll.
David S. Kong: Very, very fair. Go ahead, acrobatics.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 23.
Tim Sackton: 25.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So.
David S. Kong: This moment is 1 that this day has been a long day. It's been a long day. It's been a long battle.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But all of your training over this past stretch, and it feels like a lifetime of training has been compressed into these hours.
David S. Kong: All comes together in this orchestrated moment of pure fucking beauty. You feel the resonance of Zeno, like, shimmering through the entire body. All of your systems are aligned. Your power and potential is maximized through Sculpit. You feel Little Tony right now, and all of the energy from Little Tony is surging through this whole system, and Heska is complete acrobatic.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Mastery leaps up through the air, takes the giant stone wall, perfectly smashes it right through the cockpit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of the Dreadnought, doing…
David S. Kong: 40d12 plus 150 damage.
Mike Sackton: It's like, this is like, these dice numbers are too big to ever roll, not on D&D Beyond. We would be adding D12s for like 20 minutes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: See if we can hit the limit of the screen.
Tim Sackton: Well, with this many dice, you don't actually have to roll, you can just take the average.
Eric Rosenbaum: air.
David S. Kong: No.
Tim Sackton: So 260 plus. What did you say? Plus 125.
David S. Kong: Plus 150, because of all the… the…
Tim Sackton: so…
David S. Kong: but I'll give it a plus 150.
Tim Sackton: 300 and 410 damage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, 410 damage?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, you all successfully.
Mike Sackton: the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: bring down the Dreadnought, which crashes into the shore and is wrecked after…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The perfect strike from the Wanderer at his mall.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Amazing job. The other ship…
David S. Kong: You destroy easily. There's one other ship left, but you make short work of it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm going to immediately, like, as soon as the Dreadnought is down, go over to the two Travelers to cast Revivify on them.
David S. Kong: and.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hold on just there.
David S. Kong: Little, little, little fan art.
Eric Rosenbaum: other.
David S. Kong: Yes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, okay.
David S. Kong: You head over to the ship.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's it, yes, and I am hustling because I need to get there before they've been dead for 1 minute.
David S. Kong: You do not sense life forms on that ship.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, because they're dead, or… there's no bodies there?
David S. Kong: Because because they're dead or you I mean at least.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So I'm there to cast Revivify, so if they've been dead for…
Mike Sackton: It brings them back from the dead.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): brings.
David S. Kong: Oh, wow. Okay. All right. Nice.
Tim Sackton: my message.
David S. Kong: Did you text me, or was it on Zoom?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: On Zoom.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): us.
David S. Kong: What happens?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So they,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Pop back up again. They are… okay, so, Revivify.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The creature revives with 1 hit point.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It does not restore any missing body parts if they have missing body parts.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So they're both up and on death's door, and I'll give them a little bit, I'll give them some,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Some…
David S. Kong: Wait, so do you have, in general, have healing magic?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'll give them each a healing word.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): On top of that.
David S. Kong: So when you get there, you realize that one of them is actually dead, and the other one is bloody, still living, but like…
David S. Kong: About to die. Like, death… death saving throw away from death. But it's still alive.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Revivify for one and Healing Word for the other.
David S. Kong: Revivify doesn't do anything.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Vivify doesn't do anything.
David S. Kong: But you do Healing Word on, on, it's just, it's just Shy now, the guy.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: And Tony, there's something else now that you've kind of like, as you've gotten to this space and things have kind of, you know, the dreadnought battle's over a little bit.
David S. Kong: You suddenly realize, because the ship crash is actually not that far from the location of the dreadnought crash.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You realize… You are sensing beings in the dreadnought.
David S. Kong: And not like 1 or 2 beings, but like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hundreds.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of beings. Inside the Dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… Even more than that, you.
David S. Kong: You realize that the beings, it's like
David S. Kong: It's hard to describe it any other way, but it feels like they're children.
David S. Kong: But, like, hundreds of them.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll… Relay that, and
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wait, wait, who's the one who's still alive?
David S. Kong: Aksha. Or sorry, Ashai.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sure.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What the hell's going on? What… what is this? I'm…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There's beings of some kind inside that thing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I don't know.
David S. Kong: I mean, this is… This is a warship. I don't know why there'd be beings inside other than…
David S. Kong: The pilots.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, I'll link back up with the others then and say,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Should we go in? You wanna take a look?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: as you… approach the dreadnought.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Which is now crashed into… The side of the island.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Tony, you sense the… the.
David S. Kong: Beings are this like these enter these life signatures like kind of in the middle of the ship like that There is the giant there was like a giant like reactor thing that's kind of in the bottom This is like kind of middle back.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Shit.
David S. Kong: But you've got a pretty clear sense of where they are.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Get in there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How are you? You're just, I mean, and there's definitely wreckage. Like there's like holes and spaces you could try to like fly in if you want to, or you just go, go fly directly in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, why not? I feel pretty confident.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, is everybody joining? Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: You guys doing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Any… any… any… anything? Just going… just… just flying in?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We'll, we'll, we'll… We'll take care of ourselves if we need to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah. Okay. All right. So, you you you fly in and, you know, basically there's a lot of damage and wreckage everywhere. So, there's like kind of sufficient gaps and holes for you to, you know, kind of navigate your way through.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you end up in A room.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Inside the ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… You have never seen anything like what you're seeing inside this room because it's hard to describe.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Other than just to show it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But… It looks like there are just organisms, all kinds of weird organisms like throughout this space.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they're different shapes and just things you've never seen before, like just some things that kind of look familiar to things that you may have seen and other things that
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You just have never seen before.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And Tony, there's a bunch of things happening all at once for you, because this is all a pretty overwhelming moment. Number one, since you spoke to the Dreadnought earlier.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you have a connection with the dreadnought, you can sense for sure that the dreadnought is dying.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And not only is the dreadnought dying, but the dreadnought has what feels like.
David S. Kong: Some fire burning inside of it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: that is going to explode like soon imminently. Like this whole thing is going to go up in flames.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Very, very soon.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can communicate that urgency to everybody else here as well.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And the other thing that is kind of interesting about this space that you're in, there are all these kind of vessels with all these things, but in the center of the room, there's a particular area with a particular large set of chambers full of eggs.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: They don't look exactly like dragonet eggs.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: but.
David S. Kong: Close enough.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That feels… just… You're… Your blood pressure and everything is kind of, you know.
David S. Kong: But it's behind some kind of structure that looks different from all of the other structures here.
David S. Kong: I'm not gonna have you roll initiative. You can act in whatever order that you want, but you have five rounds now before the ship explodes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Are the… so all of the creatures that are in here are just, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Running around, and they're all.
David S. Kong: No, they're all, they're all, they're all, they're all, trapped.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's, like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's basically… it's like a specimen vault. It's like everything is, like, inside some kind of a weird… but everything's locked up. They're all… they're all, like, behind some kind of a… something.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So you have 5 rounds, every one of you gets an action to do something, anything you want.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We're almost done.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We can do 3 rounds. Let's do 3 rounds.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then the ship exploded, or then… bad things were gonna happen. I mean… I'm…
Tim Sackton: I will look around at everybody, like…
Tim Sackton: I think at this point, Haska is just like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: Completely overwhelmed, right? Like, what do we even do with this?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: When Tony says the ship's gonna explode, I'm just gonna be like Should we just run?
Mike Sackton: runaway.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Grab something interesting or shiny and run away, yes.
Eric Rosenbaum: Everybody grab a skin.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Speak with animals.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, go for it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And say,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Guys, what are you guys all doing here? What's your deal? I'm Lil Tony, it's very nice to meet you, it's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, welcome to our islands, it's very nice here, there's all sorts of things, there's armor crabs and, you know, seagulls and stuff, but like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What's your story, guys?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Help us.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just help us.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You aren't gonna, like, eat us or anything, right?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Help us. Please. We're trapped.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, right. Fuck. Okay, guys, we have to, let all of the animals out, because, you know.
David S. Kong: Please, help us.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): guys, you know?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What? What?
Tim Sackton: How do you know they're not lying to you?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Look at him! Come on!
David S. Kong: What do you mean?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This whole place is gonna blow up in, like…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The time it takes us to count to 20?
David S. Kong: It's gonna blow up in a few minutes, yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I find the one I quickly scan around looking for the most identifiably cute looking thing.
Eric Rosenbaum: From the perspective…
David S. Kong: Thank you, thanks.
Eric Rosenbaum: Dragonite.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Which would be like anything that's like even remotely Lizard-like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or scaly, or winged, or anything.
David S. Kong: I mean, the most thing that's resonant to all of you is the thing that looks like dragon eggs in the very center of the room. There's like a specific chamber that looks like it's got a whole bunch of dragon eggs that's right in the middle of the room.
Mike Sackton: Okay?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It, like…
Mike Sackton: doing.
David S. Kong: If I pick a thing, that would be a thing that you…
Mike Sackton: Yeah, let's take that.
Eric Rosenbaum: I go straight to it and try to open it. Yes.
David S. Kong: Are all of you going?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Sure.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, all hubs, you know.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna cast Summon Draconic Spirit, but why don't you…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What are you doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The expert.
David S. Kong: Can you, and Sculpit, don't forget that you have like teleportation abilities.
Mike Sackton: Right, I can just teleport there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Can I teleport to the eggs?
David S. Kong: Yeah, but you can also teleport things out, right?
Mike Sackton: Can I?
Eric Rosenbaum: Just so we don't die, yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I haven't tried. I will try to teleport somebody else.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you definitely feel like you can teleport yourself and other things if you wanted to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm gonna like go grab some eggs and teleport out. Does it work?
David S. Kong: works.
Mike Sackton: Like, how far can I go?
David S. Kong: How far are you trying to go?
Mike Sackton: Back to the library.
David S. Kong: You can make it there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Roll, actually, roll a,
David S. Kong: Roll an insight check?
Mike Sackton: thing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: You can do it.
David S. Kong: You're able to take some eggs or whatever you want to grab.
Mike Sackton: Yeah. I was grabbing a bunch of eggs.
David S. Kong: Okay?
David S. Kong: So, we'll do…
David S. Kong: You can do this 3 times, if you wanna go back and forth, you can do this 3 times.
Mike Sackton: at… Sure, I'll, I'll, do it.
Mike Sackton: Hold on one second,
Mike Sackton: I I will.
Mike Sackton: Well, other… I'll just… is three times enough time to get, like, all the… how many eggs are there?
David S. Kong: There's a lot. There's a lot. You're not gonna be able to get all of them. You can get… you can get, like, a good, like, 10 or 20 of them, if you wanted.
David S. Kong: While, while Heska is, or sorry, while Sculpid is doing this, is anybody else trying to do anything else?
Mike Sackton: Hold on, can you make me bigger again?
Tim Sackton: Sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: her.
Mike Sackton: Can I carry more eggs if I was in large?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: I had a bag or something, didn't I?
Mike Sackton: Anybody have a bag?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Good point.
Mike Sackton: like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Is this room…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: In an exterior wall of the, of the ship.
David S. Kong: The ceiling is…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Is the ship made of stone by any chance or that part of the ceiling?
David S. Kong: It is not, unfortunately.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Brett.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, and are there any doors or exits out of this room? Like, can we evacuate things directly? There are. Oh, yeah. Okay. I mean, there's holes blown throughout the
Audio shared by David S. Kong: from the whole… from the damage of the ship. There's definitely, like… Okay. You can fly out of this room. You can fly out of this room. So, I'm gonna… I'm gonna cast Summon Draconic Spirit, and the way that this works when Little Tony does it is rather than just, like, summoning a dragon out of nowhere.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: He convinces all of, like, the bits and pieces and random stuff of the room to come together in the form of a giant dragonet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's, like, 30 feet tall.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Nice.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And so he… he climbs up on top of one of the barrels that's flipped over, and he turns around to face the whole room, and he says.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Pebbles!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Railings! Light bulbs!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You don't know me, and I don't know you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): But this, in our greatest.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hour of need.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We will come together!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We will work together. We will rescue our animal friends.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Despite all of the disgusting fur that covers some of them.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: change.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We will set them free nonetheless.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And, you see, like, all the, you know, the bits of.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The rubble and the metal pipes and the sections of gantry and walkway that have kind of dislodged and the portions of the roof that have fallen down all start to wiggle over and very quickly take the form of this enormous dragonet that just…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Goes from cage to cage just in a single swipe of its paw, you know, breaking off a dozen cages at once.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And then whatever's in it starts to scamper away out the holes in the side of the ship.
David S. Kong: Okay, amazing. Yeah, you're… I mean, I'm imagining this kind of, like, Akira, like, ensemblage of, like, you know, like, just found materials into, like, a giant dragonette that is now smashing open cages, and yeah, like, stuff is escaping, there are things running around.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sculpit is also effectively now, has moved a bunch of eggs directly into the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Heska and, and,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zenor, is there anything you're are you hype manning? Are you is there anything just supporting?
David S. Kong: Well, whatever, anything…
Tim Sackton: I'm making…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm making.
Tim Sackton: Sculpt it big so he can carry more things.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Perfect.
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno's like, okay, yeah, it's cool. He's got the egg situation under control, but.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So I go back to the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Now open cage of the one cutest entity.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And I'm like… I'll help you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You individually, now come here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And I boop it out.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You have a little football carry.
Eric Rosenbaum: And fly out, rescuing my little friend.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, you all successfully.
David S. Kong: these methods.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's definitely saved, like, a lot of beings.
David S. Kong: Definitely don't save everybody.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: but there's.
David S. Kong: many that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: freed And you're able to pull out some.
David S. Kong: 20-or-so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of these weird eggs that look.
David S. Kong: kind of like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm not sure exactly what they are.
David S. Kong: ring.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And sit into the water.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as all of this is happening, the ship is pulsing, and, you know, you all literally did a giant maul through the center of the thing. There's a giant reactor on the ship, the thing has been, you know, smoking and billowing, and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As you make your final escape, the entire… Massive
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Explodes, and just burns in this huge, fiery wreckage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: as the ship.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The ship explodes, and as you escape with…
David S. Kong: whatever these beings.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: are.
David S. Kong: Who knows?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It was exactly what was going on the ship, and whatever is happening in this space.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You fly out now, Just, kind of.
David S. Kong: feeling through.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What the hell is going on with this giant ship and these beings?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you go back to go and visit.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Aksha, who is.
David S. Kong: still alive.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: news.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: in the ship.
David S. Kong: Low hit points.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's… but it's still awake.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And he beckons you over.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: He says to you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They know that You're here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're not gonna stop looking for you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know what this means.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know?
David S. Kong: experience You can't stay here.
Eric Rosenbaum: If you stay here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: If you stay here, They're always gonna find you.